[Music]
[Música]
we have a bomb
tenemos una bomba
the caring Through
the caring Through
The Golden glow refle
The Golden glow refle
Smile
Smile
sh out of
sh out of
[Music]
[Música]
here
here
out on the
out on the
lak Where we stop to Rest a miles from
lak Where we stop to Rest a miles from
home but we Never this Close
home but we Never this
we Start a New life in a New kind
Close we Start a New life in a New kind
of Life Where
of Life Where
the and Sky Clear s
the and Sky
with Our heads Together We have
Clear s with Our heads Together We have
the Dream New to in the window of
the Dream New to in the window of
[Music]
[Música]
a
a
Under let's see what people are saying
Under vamos a ver qué está diciendo la
about that photograph that just went
gente sobre esa fotografía que se acaba
viral  by Antonia
de viralizar de Antonia
[Music]
[Música]
well
bien
it get Cold When we
it get Cold When we
Run pray for an [Music
Run pray for an
]
[Música]
early timeless and patience in Life we
early timeless and patience in Life we
Dance Together all [
Dance Together all
Music]
[Música]
we slep with Our
we slep with Our
heads we Had the same Dream a New Town
heads we Had the same Dream a New Town
in the window of a
in the window of a
tree going
tree going
85 Under
85 Under
Street empty free in the middle of the
Street empty free in the midle of the
Night I'll
Night I'll
DJ
DJ
the Seat Back even though you get car
the Seat Back even though you get car
sick like
sick like
[Music]
[Música]
that from the moment you B
that from the moment you B
You
You
the
the
B Where you have
B Where you have
[Music]
[Música]
ging Everything you  don't
ging Everything you don't
know you you it
know you
All You
you it All You
Don't you got
Don't you got
you
you
[Music]
[Música]
got Everything You
you got Everything You
Need
Need
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
You feel
You feel
like
like
you All the things you have squ
you All the things you have squ
feel
feel
like you could you could a Dream But You
like you could you could a Dream But You
Just see it There is Always another day
Just see it There is Always another day
for you there's [Music]
for you there's
another no day is too late there's
another no day is too late there's
Always A Way out everything you
Always A Way
got Everything you need
you you got Everything you need
Everything you
Everything you
[Music]
[Música]
need
need
got
got
[Music]
[Música]
you
you
Got
Got
[Music]
[Música]
you
you
Hold
Hold
[Music]
[Música]
the former director live tomorrow and
el Antiguo director de directo mañana y
live on Friday
directo el viernes
and let's see if on Sunday Everything depends
y vamos a ver si el domingo Todo depende
on
de
[Music]
[Música]
When it hurts like
When it hurts like
this
this
We clim the greatest
We clim the greatest
he jump down and have a
he jump down and have a
Fight and That's all like but that can
Fight and That's all like but that can
never change my mind When It's good It's
never change my mind When It's good It's
Amazing  When It's
Amazing When It's
B Easy I
B Easy I
want another  there's no
want another there's no
other When it hurts
other When it hurs
[Music]
[Música]
like
like
When it hurts like
When it hurts like
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
this Hold each other
this Hold each other
High but we Fall a
High but we Fall a
Times but i' Never say goodbye
Times but i' Never say
Leave This Stuff
goodbye Leave This Stuff
behind When It's good It
behind When It's good
's When
It's When
basy I
basy I
another
another
there it
there it
[Music]
[Música]
hur
hur
mindo
miendo
[Music]
[Música]
d
d
ah
ah
[Music]
[Música]
muat
muat
Ah you weren't listening to me Well
Ah que no me estabais escuchando bueno
nothing I was saying that I was
nada que estaba diciendo que Estaba
preparing the live
preparando el directo
eh And I found out that they're
eh Y me he encontrado con que se estan
messing with me Good night sir tasty
metiendo con buenas noches señor sabroso
tell chis every day I see you better You're
cuent chis cada día te veo mejor eres
like a Velázquez painting that gains
como un cuadro de Velázquez que gana
value with the years Well
valor con el pasar de los años pues Dios
my God I have a tremendous bad face
mío tengo hoy una mala cara tremenda
today I have a bad face Because I'm still sick
tengo hoy una mala cara Porque sigo
man I mean look I've slept
malito tío o sea mira que he dormido
as much as possible I mean I've slept I think I
todo lo posible o sea he dormido creo
woke up at like 7 or
que me he despertado como a las 7 a las
8 in the evening I've been
8 de la tarde He estado todo el tiempo
sleeping as much as possible the whole time I say to
durmiendo lo máximo posible digo para
recover and get up at  100
recuperarme y levantarme ya al 100 por
finally but I'm still not 100
fin pero todavía no estoy al 100
dude I'm still not 100 I'm not
tío todavía no estoy al 100 no estoy no
100 I'm not 100 yet I still feel uh my
estoy al 100 todavía me noto
throat is a bit loose it's still
eh flojillo la garganta todavía me
hard for me to speak much okay Well I have a
cuesta hablar mucho vale Bueno tengo un
guy who talks like this about gossip and stuff he
chico que habla así de salseos y demás
has a small channel no and these
tiene un canal pequeño no y los los
channels that are are like
canales estos que son son como Ob
Dallas Obsessed he starts to comment let's see
Dallas se pone a comentar a ver por lo
apparently the kid lives in Japan I didn't
visto El chaval vive en Japón yo esto no
know this and of course Dallas is in
lo sabía y y claro el Dallas está en
Japan Well it seems that Dallas told him
Japón Pues se ve que el Dallas le ha
Hey well what do I know let's go see each other
dicho Oye pues yo que sé vamos a vernos
and will you come with me no Or come with us we
y me acompañas no O acompáñanos que
want to go to an event or something and or The
queremos ir a un evento o algo y o El
kid must have offered he said
chaval se habrá ofrecido el ha dicho
man of course come with us he must have
hombre claro venga acompáñanos no habrá
seen the channel he must have seen more or less
visto el canal habrá visto más o menos
something of his sometime I've
alguna cosa de él alguna vez yo lo he
seen him a few times because I don't have
visto pocas veces porque yo no tengo
time to see anyone but it's
tiempo de ver nadie pero sí que es
true that the times that I've seen him The
verdad que las veces que lo he visto El
kid defends logical things and
chaval defiende cosas lógicas y habla
speaks with his head you know Total that whatever it is you can't see what he did to him like you accompanied him to an event not there in  Japan or whatever
un evento no allí en Japón o lo que sea
and they took a picture and they're all
y se han hecho una foto y están todos
with the pictures messing around because dude
con las fotos metiéndose porque tío de
really I mean the internet is so incredibly
verdad O sea internet es tan sumamente
big they're all interested in
grande están pendientes de la vida del
Dallas's life dude and they mess with everything that has to
Dallas tío y se meten con todo lo que
do with Dallas eh two
tenga que ver con el Dallas eh dos
cockroaches mutate in Japan Japan has
cucarachas mutan en Japón Japón ha
announced that they are two unique cases that
anunciado que son dos casos únicos que
luckily this won't be a
por suerte esto no será una
plague And why do they have to call them
plaga Y por qué les tiene que
Congratulations on seeing a youtuber that you
Felicidades por ver a un youtuber que te
like Although the ass face and contempt I just
gusta Aunque la cara de culo y desprecio
don't understand why they have to
Es que no entiendo por qué tienen que
comment I mean if it's not about
comentar O sea si no va
you it makes me feel sorry for in kovsky him
contigo me da penilla in kovsky él
taking them to the best cosplay event
llevándoles al mejor evento de cosplay
Javi I just wanted to tell you that I
Javi Solo quería decirte que disfruto
really enjoy your live streams sometimes I have a bad
mucho tus directos a veces tengo un mal
day and listening to the gossip Around here it
día y escuchar los chismes Por aquí me
distracts me period I don't consume any
distraen punto yo No Consumo ningún
channels but gossip
canalp pero chisme
kisses handsome muac even it hurt me when he called
besos guapo muac hasta a mí me dolió que
me out of nowhere and lays an egg I mean I do
me llame la nada y pone un huevo o sea
n't know if the egg thing is like making fun
no sé si lo del huevo es como burlándose
of his
de su
physique I hope I'm wrong No
físico ojalá me esté equivocando No
because I think they call him
porque creo que le dicen como cabeza
egg-headed or something because he shaves his head no  but
huevo o algo porque se rapa no pero
come on I hope it's not messing with
vamos Espero que no sea metiéndose con
the physique because that would be
el físico porque sería
an
una
outrage but well I don't know but it's
barbaridad pero bueno no lo sé pero es
like
como
how T Or if not it's not even something
cóm T O sea si no no es ya ni algo
newsworthy no because you say Well then it
noticiable no porque tú dices Bueno pues
is something newsworthy Dallas has
es algo noticiable el Dallas se ha
fought in Japan with someone that they would
peleado en Japón con alguien que ellos
support whoever fought with
apoyarían al que se pelearan con el
Dallas but no no it's that Dallas has
Dallas pero no no es que el Dallas se ha
met with this ikoni not with this
encontrado con ikoni este no con el
guy
chico este
and and there's a photo so nothing is
y y hay una foto pues nada est
commenting on the photo that's what the
comentando la foto eso mismo decía la
protagonist of the play I saw on Monday said
protagonista de la obra que vi el lunes
that she was a little touched and yet she
que estaba un poco tocada y con todo
did a great job it didn't show and I
hizo un gran trabajo no se le notó y yo
think that if you go out motivated to tell they
creo que si tú sales motivado a contar
notice the ills less Cheer up there's no
notan menos los males Ánimo que no hay
virus that can beat you but I'm already
virus que pueda contigo pero ya es que
exhausted man it's been many days I've
estoy agotado tío ya son muchos días Ya
been at least TR days and and I am and I
llevo por lo menos TR días y y estoy y
am exhausted I'm already
estoy agotado Ya estoy
tired I already want to be well and
cansado Ya tengo ganas de estar bien y
powerful active you know it's Friday
potente activo sabes estamos a viernes
tomorrow Saturday Sunday Monday I start
mañana sábado domingo El lunes empiezo a
training now
entrenar
Hey did you see dese with a
ya Hola viste deose con una
girl tell that gossip they haven't
chavala contar ese chisme no me han
put any of that on me let's
puesto nada de eso vamos a
[Music]
[Música]
comment let's comment that
comentar vamos a comentar que por lo
Apparently Koku has been
visto koku ha sido
reported criminally, they have
denunciado penalmente lo han
reported him because the dog, I don't know if he has
denunciado porque el perro no sé si ha
killed another dog or has done
llegado a matar otro perro o le ha hecho
enough harm to another dog, okay, so
bastante daño a otro perro vale o sea
Cosu has these dogs,
cosu tiene estos perros
eh Let's see, I don't know what your
eh A ver yo respecto a esto no sé qué
opinion is on this, but I really
opinión tenéis pero a a mí me dan mucho
respect them. Some dogs, some breeds of
respeto Algunos perros algunas razas de
dogs. I know that there are a lot of people who
perros Yo sé que hay mucha gente que
say that they are like mantras, not
dice que son como mantras no leyendas
urban legends, that dogs, no matter their
urbanas que los perros da igual la
appearance or breed, they are all like
apariencia y la raza que son todos como
s, look, animals are
s a ver los animales son
animals, that's why we have to start from
animales eso tenemos que partir de de
that basis, I mean, animals, no matter how
esa base o sea los animales por más
good they are, some come out better,
buenos que sean algunos salen mejores
others come out worse, whatever you
otros salen peores vale lo que tú
want, but in the end, animals are
quieras pero al final los animales son
animals, they are not civilized and
animales no son personas civilizadas y
educated people, and all that nonsense, okay, he has
educadas y y todo el rollo vale ha
killed, no, the dogs have killed another
matado no los perros han matado a otro
dog, no So what do you want me to
perro no Entonces qué quieres que te
tell you, eh, it's not the same. Maybe if
diga eh No es lo mismo A lo mejor si de
suddenly a Coke or a
repente le entra una neura a un coke o a
Chihuahua gets nervous, which in itself can already
un chihuahua que ya de por sí te puede
hurt you, not a dog, a dog, but it
hace daño no un perro un perro pero no
's not the same. Maybe
es lo mismo A lo mejor que le que se le
a Chihuahua goes crazy as opposed to a
cruce un cable a un chihuahua que a un
rockweiler of this or rather this
rockweiler de esto o sea es que esto te
kills you eh It's that this kills you then there are
mata eh Es que esto te mata entonces hay
many people who say no it doesn't matter no and the
mucha gente que dice no da igual no y el
typical video of rockweiler with the baby
típico vídeo del rockweiler con el bebé
no as if it were something
no como si fuera algo
harmless I have dogs I have dogs and there
inofensivo yo hay perros yo hay perro y
are breeds of dogs
hay razas de perro
that let's see that I don't know They give me
que que la a ver que no sé A mí me dan
respect they give me respect okay I'm not going
respeto a mí me dan respeto vale no voy
to say that they are dangerous dogs in Yes
a decir que sean perros peligrosos en Sí
because I imagine that it will depend on each
porque me imagino que dependerá de cada
one from How it is from the education that they
uno desde Cómo es desde la educación que
have since they were little I don't know they are
tiene desde pequeño No lo sé los son
how they are raised I don't know okay In the end I
como se crían No lo sé vale Yo al final
think that it will affect How you
creo que sí que afectará Como tú los
raise them and how you educate them from childhood and
cres y como los eduques desde pequeño y
all that but in the end an
todo el rollo pero que al final un
animal is an
animal es un
animal or rather in the end an animal is an
animal o sea al final un animal es un
animal So I I for example It's that
animal Entonces yo yo por ejemplo Es que
in my case uh I
yo en mi caso eh yo
know I've known of incidents in
conozco yo he conocido movidas en
children's parks where suddenly
parques de niños que de repente a
someone who was walking their dog has
alguien que iba paseando el perro se le
escaped and the dog has gone one of
ha escapado y se ha ido el perro un
these dogs for a little boy and
perro de estos para un chiquillo y
I know one I'm not going to say who it is in
conozco uno no voy a decir quién es por
case it bothers him if I
no por si le molestase que lo que lo
tell him no  but it's someone that you
contase no pero es alguien que que
know, I don't remember if it was a nephew,
conocéis no me acuerdo si era un sobrino
I think it was a nephew who was with
creo que era un sobrino que estaba con
the nephew in the park and a person
el sobrino en el parque y una persona
who was walking with one of these dogs,
que iba paseando con un perro de estos
the dog got away and hit him,
el perro se le escapó y le dio al de
suddenly they were walking, it got away and
repente paseando se le escapó y se fue
the dog became a kid and grabbed his
el perro para chiquillo y le cogió la
face well he made a slit in half his
cara pues lo ha echo aquí una raja media
face he threw his face down for the rest of his
cara le echo la cara abajo para toda la
life, his face was already marked, you
vida ya señalada la
know, these are things that and well and he could have
sabes son cosas que y bueno y podría
stayed there
haberse quedado
no Javi are there special regulations for
ahí no Javi hay normativa especial para
these dogs I think there are dogs that I
esos perros Yo es que hay perros que
consider that, let's see, they give me
Considero que a ver a mí me dan
respect, there are dogs that, I mean, it's like
respeto yo hay perros que o sea es como
suddenly, I mean, all animals
si de repente o sea todos los animales
can't be kept in the house, they can't be
no se pueden tener en casa no se pueden
kept in the neighborhoods, they can't be kept, there
tener los barrios no se pueden
are dogs that
tener a mí hay perros que me dan
scare me it's that, it's that, it's that this kills you, this kills you,
miedo es que eso es que esto te mata
this is that he suddenly gets it,
esto te mata esto se le coge de repente
no, but it's that you don't understand
tal no pero es que tú no entiendes de
dogs, it's that they are trained, it's that I don't know what,
perro es que se educan es que no sé qué
well, yes, probably But you keep it in
bueno sí probablemente Pero tú tenlo en
your house
tu casa
and anyway, apparently he's had a
y en fin pues por lo visto ha tenido una
problem okay, let's see what you put me
movida vale a ver qué es lo que me pones
here's some news there's a video it
aquí una noticia hay un vídeo ni tan
's not even the same thing as
siquiera es lo mismo que se le cruce un
a strong person like coscu himself getting crossed over the wire
cable a una persona fuerte como el mismo
who could beat up
coscu que podría reventar a puñetazos a
whoever confronts him than
quien se le enfrenta a que se ponga
a 150 year old girl who's not
agresiva una chavalita de 150 que no
half a
tiene media
nut getting aggressive I don't understand your point I
torta no he entendido tu punto Me
imagine that maybe you're comparing one breed
imagino que comparas a lo mejor una raza
with another No maybe not
con otra No a lo mejor no
eh It's not the breed it's the
eh Es que no es la raza es que es la
breed the strength that they have the instinct that they
raza la fuerza que tiene el instinto que
have there are dogs that are for houses there are
tiene hay hay perros que son de casa hay
dogs that are more there are breeds that are more
perros que son más hay razas que son más
playful more harmless more
juguetonas más inofensivas más
family oriented then there's a dog that is the
familiares entonces hay perro quey es
animals don't come out like mammals they
el los animales no salen como mamíferos
behave as they learn that
se comportan como lo aprendan que los
coscu's dogs behave badly
perros de coscu se comporten mal
confirms how we've seen
confirma cómo lo hemos visto comportarse
him behave Today it
él Hoy
is they are dogs that are evolutionarily
es son perros que evolutivamente están
prepared for field work and
preparados para trabajo de campo y
protection they are not bad But
protección no son malos Pero no es lo
going out for drinks with Mike Tyson is not the same as going out for drinks
mismo salir de copas con Mike Tyson que
with Pepe
con Pepe
fly of course of course
vuela claro
I I am a dog that I don't I don't go to
claro yo yo es un perro que yo no a mí
see me it doesn't make me uncomfortable Me
no me a ver a mí no me a mí me incomoda
too It's that I am  I'm really mad I
Yo también Es que soy más cago de la
also tell you no but it makes me
cuenta también te digo no pero a mí a mí
uncomfortable
me incomoda
m when Maybe I'm sitting in a
m cuando A lo mejor estoy sentado en una
square or in a park or whatever and there are
plazoleta o en un parque o lo que sea y
people with those dogs okay
hay gente con esos perros vale que ya
then you can tell me no but it
luego tú me puede decir no pero es que
depends on the owner it's that if the owner
depende del dueño es que si el dueño le
has taught him well since he was little it's that I don't
ha enseñado bien desde pequeño es que no
know what in the end Fran Well more than you don't
sé qué al final Fran Bueno más que tú no
know You're not going to I'm not going to know
lo sabes No lo vas a no lo voy a saber
I don't but in the end animals always They
yo no pero al final los animales siempre
are animals no I mean it doesn't mean that at a
Son animales no O sea no quita que en un
given moment
momento dado
eh he has an attack or he gives I don't know the
eh le dé un Arrebato o le dé no sé la
truth I have no idea I don't know how to
verdad no tengo ni idea no sé cómo
explain it but no I don't trust I no I don't
explicarlo pero no no confío yo no yo no
trust
confío
in something like that 100% not in how
en en algo así al 100% no en en como lo
the dog has been raised in how he has been
hayan criado al perro en como lo hayan
taught exactly and without a muzzle Of course
enseñado exactamente y sin bozal Claro
because obviously if the dog has a
porque evidentemente si el perro lleva
bosal which I think I think in fact
bosal que creo que creo que de hecho
those breeds always have to have a
esas razas siempre tienen que ir con
bosal no Or that's not like
bosal no O eso no es
that I think I believe that they always have to have a
así Creo que lo creo que siempre tienen
muzzle
que ir con bzal
eh I think they always have to have a
eh creo que siempre tienen que ir con
bosar eh to me a  koker bit me and
bosar eh a mí un koker me mordió y me
left me marked forever my rockweiler has
dejó marcado para siempre mi rockweiler
n't done anything good let's
no ha hecho nada bueno ya vamos a
start with that I'm really not going to
empezar con eso De verdad no voy a
enter into that debate I'm
entrar en ese debate yo te estoy
telling you that they give me respect it
diciendo que que a mí me dan respeto no
's not the same a coke a Coque
es lo mismo un coke un Coque sí te
can bite you but the coqu are crazy
pueden morder pero los coqu están Loc
lost apparently you know but that the
Perdidos por lo visto sabes pero que el
coke can bite you Well of course and and the
coke te puede morder Pues claro y y el
jorai can bite you too the jorai
jorai también te puede morder los jorai
have a bad a bad temper every day and
tienen una mal una mala [__] tod día y
a bad mood that is crazy but a youride
un mal humor que flipa pero un youride
comes to hit you comes to hit you a
te viene a pegar un te viene a pegar un
bite and you go like this boom and you send him
un bocado y le haces así pum y lo mandas
to Carmona but a dog like that that doesn't
a Carmona pero un perro de esos que no
give you time is that like that and it kills you And it breaks your
te da tiempo es que eso te así y te mata
neck I mean That one is that no it's not that it bites you it's that it
Y te parte el cuello o sea Ese es que no
breaks your
te no es que te muerda es que se te
neck do you understand me or I mean it's that no I'm not
cuello me entiendes o sea es que no no
going to enter into the debate now of Oh you don't
voy a entrar ya en el debate de Ay no
understand about dogs Oh Because look I
entiendes de perro Ay Porque mira yo
have a video of my rockweiler with the
tengo un vídeo de mi rockweiler con el
baby on top of her I'm not going to enter into that debate it
bebé encima no voy a entrar a ese debate
gives me respect or  let it be nature
a mí me da respeto o sea la naturaleza
is nature
es la naturaleza
okay the most appropriate thing is to have it on a
vale lo más adecuado es tenerlo con
leash and muzzled exactly man Ramon
Correa y bzal exactamente hombre Ramón
Today is the day
Hoy es el día
I drew blood from a Rottweiler that
yo he sacado sangre a un rottweiler que
wasn't tied up or even muzzled and the
no estaba atado ni con bzal y estaba el
poor thing was more scared than anything with the group
pobre más asustado que nada con el grupo
of students that were on practice
de alumnos que estábamos en prácticas
but if it had gotten aggressive it would
pero si se llega a poner agresivo nos
hit us hard let's just let's be honest but
pega buen viaje las cosas como son pero
you too picking up and drawing
es que tú también cogiendo y sacándole
blood from the dog without muzzling it I have a
sangre al perro sin bozar Yo tengo un
Pit Bull and he's very well behaved but the truth
pitbull y es muy educado pero la verdad
is that he's playful and when
es que es juguetón y cuando los perros
small dogs or children see him it's better for him to
chicos o los niños lo ven es mejor que
have his muzzle on because you don't know how he
tenga su bozal porque uno no saben cómo
might react Of course but in the
puede reaccionar Claro pero es que al
end he's an animal You
final es un animal
know that no matter how much trust you
Sabes que por más confianza que tú
have And no matter how much you say no but it's because
tengas Y por más que tú digas no pero es
since he was little he's been educated with
que desde pequeño se la ha educado desde
love in the end he's an animal I mean
el cariño al final es un animal no O sea
you don't know at any given moment how he
tú no sabes en un momento dado Cómo
might react or that he might suddenly
puede reaccionar o que él de repente
misinterpret a movement from someone or
malinterprete un movimiento de alguien o
something and think it's an attack and
de algo y y se crea que es un ataque y
hit you in the end an animal is
te pega un viaje al final un animal es
an
un
animal in the neighborhood because more or rather
animal en el barrio porque más o seaar
That obviously there was Here I have  I'm selling myself.
Que obviamente hubi Aquí tengo a véndome
Look, I did a program about
Ya mira yo hice un programa sobre perros
dangerous dogs, a whole program, and I
peligrosos eh un programa entero y me
spent almost months preparing it. Look, I
pasé casi se meses preparándolo Mira yo
did a program about dangerous dogs,
hice un programa sobre perros peligrosos
a whole program, and I spent almost
eh un programa entero y me pasé casi se
months preparing it, talking to people,
meses preparándolo hablando con gente
dog owners, breeders. At the
con dueños de perros con criadores al
end of the day, they are dogs that if you
final del día son perros que si tú los
teach them from a young age, well, and the, and the,
enseñas desde pequeños eh bien y el y y
and the caretaker or the owner keeps them
el y el cuidador o el dueño los tiene
well, well balanced, they are not
bien bien equilibrados no son perros
dangerous dogs, okay, but they are potentially
peligrosos vale pero son potencialmente
dangerous, as they were called before. What does it
peligrosos que les llamaban antes Qué
mean? Well, the strength they
quiere decir pues que la fuerza que
have is gone if a Chihuahua goes crazy,
tienen se les va si se le va la olla un
well, it can bite you. And yes, it hurts,
Chihuahua eh pues te puede pegar un
but it's not a problem.
mordisco Y si te duele pero no pasa nada
If a rottweiler bites you or a
si te pega un mordisco un rot wier o te
pitbull bites you, eh, it has a
pega un mordisco un pitbull eh tiene una
bite. Maybe 3,000 times
mordida A lo mejor 3000 veces es más
stronger than a Chihuahua, it's a question
fuerte que un chihuahua es una cuestión
of what dogs you want to have. And how you
de qué perros quieres tener Y cómo los
want to relate them. So, people
quieres relacionar entonces la gente
obviously want stronger dogs, they
obviamente quiere perros más fuertes
want bigger dogs, above all, it always depends
quiere perros más sobre todo siempre va
on the person's profile.
con el perfil de la persona
There is a program, for example, about
eh Hay un progama por ejemplo de de
dog training for women.
entrenamiento de perros para mujeres
abused women who are afraid of their
maltratadas mujeres que tienen miedo de
ex-husbands And then they prepare those
los exmarido Y entonces se preparan esos
dogs to live with them and
perros para que vivan con ellas y las
protect them from everything. They are dogs that are
protejan de todo son perros que están
prepared to protect, so there are
preparados para proteger entonces hay
times when they go a little crazy and that's what
veces que se les va un poco la pinza y
happens. And of course, it's not the same to
es lo que pasa y claro no es lo mismo
have one dog as to have five dogs of
tener un perro que tener cinco perros de
that type. They are a pack. At the end of the day,
ese tipo son una manada al final del día
if one attacks, they all follow.
si uno ataca van todos detrás
And it's an option that many people have,
e es una opción que tiene mucha gente
but it works if you have a
pero que funciona si tienes una finca
large property and they are there to protect the property or
grande y están para proteger la finca o
in the countryside, in a city. Really, one
en el campo en una ciudad realmente un
of those dogs can do a lot more
perro de esos puede hacer muchísimo más
damage than people think. So it's
daño de lo que la gente piensa entonces
not that the dog is bad, it's that you
no es que el perro sea malo es que tú
can have one that you can control. You can't control the
puedes tener uno que puedes controlar tú
four of them. We
cuatro no los controlas
hadn't gone into that. Thank you, Fran. I hadn't. I hadn't
no habíamos entrado Gracias Fran no
gone into that. I'm terrible,
entrado estoy fatal
eh. We hadn't gone into that subject. It
eh No habíamos entrado en ese tema
's still very valid that it gives you a little bit of a scare.
Todavía es muy válido que te de cosita
Because also, you never know how
Porque además Uno nunca sabe cómo las
other people raise their animals. Well, of
demás personas crían sus animales Bueno
course, the first thing is that you don't know, but
claro lo primero es que tú no sabes pero
the second is that even if you believe it well,
lo segundo es que aunque tú lo cres bien
in the end, an animal is an animal, it
al final un animal es un animal es que
's neither good nor bad, I mean, it's not that it's
no es ni Bueno ni malo o sea no es que
neither good nor bad.  It's that it's an animal
sea ni Bueno ni malo es que es un animal
and suddenly Maybe something,
y es que de repente A lo mejor una cosa
a movement that a human being makes, a
un movimiento que haga un ser humano un
car passing by and honking, a motorcycle
coche que pase y que pite una moto que
falling, or maybe a child suddenly getting
se caiga o sea un niño que de repente le
hit by a ball, I mean, you don't know how,
pega un balonazo O sea tú no sabes cómo
you don't know how it's going to react, it's an
tú no sabes cómo va a reaccionar es un
animal and maybe it's not bad, it's not
animal y a lo mejor no es malo él no es
bad, but it's an animal and suddenly
malo pero él es un animal y de repente a
maybe it feels attacked Or it feels
lo mejor se siente atacado O se siente
in a hostile environment that is not its own
en un ambiente hostil que no es el suyo
and it attacks you in defense because it believes that it
y te ataca en defensa porque se cree que
is
se está
defending itself, something else, what
defendiendo otra cosa lo que ha dicho
Fran said is the issue of CCU that we
Fran que es el tema de ccu que no
hadn't gotten into that, well, a
habíamos entrado en eso bueno una
Revolution in the neighborhood because it's not just that you
Revolución en el barrio porque más que
have one dog, but now you
ya no es que tengas un perro de eso que
have four or
ya es que tengas cuatro o
five, now you have four or
cinco que ya es que tengas cuatro o
five, in the end, animals are animals
cinco al final los animales son animales
and in the end,
y al final
eh, I don't know much because
eh Ya no sé yo mucho porque eso no
I don't understand
entiendo yo
much, but I imagine that it will be
mucho pero me imagino que irá
related to what Fran said, not
relacionado con lo que ha dicho Fran no
that this dog is not that dangerous,
que este perro no es que sea peligroso
yes, every dog, no, but
en Sí cada perro no pero sí
potentially dangerous, of course, when it comes to, when it goes
potencialmente peligroso claro a la hora
crazy, it
de a la hora de que se le cruce un cable
's not the same  a chihuahua that is not
no es lo mismo un chihuahua que este no
and apart but not only in
y aparte pero ya no solamente en la
strength but in El Coco Not in El Coco
fuerza sino en El Coco No en el coco
each one each dog each breed in a
cada uno cada perro cada raza de una
way but apart it is not the
forma pero aparte es que no es la
bite it is that as far as I
mordida es que hasta donde yo tengo
understand correct me if I'm wrong
entendido corregirme si me equivoco
even giving I understand the the the
hasta dando yo tengo entendido el el el
Ros dance this is not only that it
Ros baile este no es solamente que te
bites you it bites you it breaks your
muerda es que te muerde te parte el
neck
cuello
no I mean it's going to kill you when it attacks you it's going
no O sea va a matarte cuando te ataca va
to
a
kill a kiss
matar un beso
inco I mean what's going on man I'm terrible you can't
inco O sea qué va tío estoy fatal no me
hear my voice I'm terrible man I'm
escuchas la voz estoy fatal tío estoy
terrible the truth is that I don't know
fatal la verdad es que estoy ya no sé
what to do because the truth is that so many
qué hacer porque la verdad es que tantas
hours in bed also despairs me
horas en la cama también me desespero
man That obviously there were other uh
tío Que obviamente hubieran otros eh
other incidents with these these three
otos incidentes con estos estos tres
dogs and that well obviously c that
perros y que bueno obviamente c que
Call Martin and except should have been
Llama Martín y salvo debería haber sido
responsible with this issue and therefore
responsable con este tema y Por ende
now they have just reported it this is
ahora lo lo acaban de denunciar esto es
the last moment it was now apart they
el último momento fue ahora aparte le
can get the dogs taken away the
pueden llegar a sacar los perros los
dogs in the neighborhood they have already
perros del barrio ya se los
removed them pu but I send a kiss to
retiraron pu per le mando un beso a
Carla that not from primary I mean not for
Carla que no de primario O sea que no la
many years I hope she is okay let's
muchísimos años Espero que esté bien a
see if we will see  if it's the same
ver si vamos a ver si es la misma
person yes it is her
persona sí es ella
look Well but [ __ ] what
mir Bueno pero [__] qué ha
happened we were on another shift tomorrow afternoon
pasado éramos otro turno mañana tarde
but I remember it well I hope she
pero me la rec acuerdo bueno Espero que
's okay then tremendous we'll see how
esté bien entonces tremendo veremos Cómo
the complaint goes Well a Revolution
sigue la denuncia Bueno una Revolución
in the But what
en el Pero qué es lo que ha
happened you have put places you have
pasado que me has puesto lugares me has
put a video there super short one of
puesto un vídeo ahí super corto una de
the neighbors and they attacked her ferociously
las vecinas y la atacaron ferozmente
last
útimo
moment the least expected day God forbid
momento el día menos pensado Dios no lo
the dogs eat the coscu
quiera los perros se comen al coscu
because what recklessness having several of
porque qué temeridad tener varios de
those and facing those four big
esos y enfrentarse a esos cuatro
dogs is not like facing Germán
perrazos no es como enfrentarse a Germán
I hope they have space to run because
Ojalá tengan campo para correr porque
on top of that in an apartment creatures of the
encima en un piso criaturas del
lord today it
señor hoy
is in Peru it is mandatory that
es en Perú es obligatorio que lleguen
bzal arrive various breeds and I think it's correct
bzal varias razas y creo que es correcto
my German cried the first few times
mi germana lloraba las primeras veces
when we put the dog in because the
cuando le pusimos al perro porque el
dog cried but then they both got
perro lloraba pero luego los dos se
used to it my sister and the dog and
acostumbraron mi hermana y el perro y
they walk safely they go out for walks without
andan seguros ellos salen a pasear sin
risk of him doing harm and of her
riesgo de que él haga daño y de que ella
passing of course
pase claro
Eh well let's see of
Eh bueno a ver
course well Mariana they reported or rather it
claro bueno Mariana denunciaron o sea
is criminally reported coscu ah it was
está denunciado penalmente coscu ah era
gra here in Spain I don't know right now
gra aquí en España no sé yo ahora mismo
How is the situation if you have to have a
Cómo es el percal si tienes que tener
muzzle or not I understand that yes but I don't
bzal o no Yo entiendo que sí pero no lo
know I understand that yes that the dogs so it
sé entiendo que sí que los perros así
was something fun what vicia
que era algo divertido lo que vicia
penal kcu who is a streamer for those who do
penal kcu que es un streamer para los
not know uses the
que no conocen usa utiliza las redes
social networks Twitch and YouTube to make himself
sociales Twitch y YouTube para para dar
known and makes
darse a conocer y hace interacciones
social lases interactions with singers also this
lases socialo a cantantes también este
character was criminally reported
personaje lo denunciaron penalmente
because he has three dogs in a
porque tiene tres per en un barrio
gated community in the north zone those three dogs
cerrado en zona norte esos tres perros
escaped and they killed the dog of one
se escaparon y Mataron al perro de una
of the neighbors the three
de las vecinas se escaparon los tres
dogs escaped or in other words the three dogs
perros o sea que los tres perros se
escaped and they killed the dog of a
escaparon y Mataron al perro de una
neighbor and they attacked her ferociously this
vecina y la atacaron ferozmente esta
neighbor is called Carla and from school be
vecina se llama Carla y del colegio sea
ccu lives in one of these
ccu vive en un barrio de estos
closed neighborhoods okay it's the same as they have killed
cerrad vale sea igual que han matado a
a dog Imagine that there are
un perro Imagínate que hay
children, let's say I don't know if a child I tell you and
niños vamos yo no sé si niño te digo y
adults no I mean a couple of
adultos no O sea un par de perros de
those dogs take on an adult
esos se cargan a un adulto
too be a couple of those dogs
también sea un par de perros de esos
Well look Well it turns out that cocu
Pues mira Pues resulta ser que cocu
lived in one I don't know which one but
vivía en uno no sé en cuál de ellas pero
well one of these neighborhoods that are
bueno un barrio de estos que son
closed Okay
cerrados Vale
and and ha  caught the dogs they have
y y ha cogido los perros se se le han
escaped According to what they
escapado Según
say from the house and they have been roaming around the
dicen de la casa y han estado por el
neighborhood while he takes a
barrio rulando mientras que él duerme la
nap
siesta
and they have killed a neighbor's dog
y y han matado a un perro de una vecina
But well they have killed a dog a
Pero bueno que han matado un perro una
neighbor maybe they could have
vecina sea que podía haber matado
even killed more
incluso a a más
people school you went to Argentina
personas colegio fuiste a la Argentina
model dosimo no that's what I was going to tell you doxe
model dosimo no eso te iba a decir doxe
adsim no way but they have doxed all over
adsim no sea pero han doxeado por toda
the face here the house
la cara aquí la casa
no
no
3 the dogs got loose obviously they
3 los perros se soltaron obviamente
attacked car and his dog it was already known
atacaron a car y a su per ya se sabía
where he lived or they doxed all over the face his
dnde vivía o han doado por la cara su
dog died but Carla well Carla
perra murió pero Carla bien Carla se
had to be hospitalized because of the bites from
tuvo que internar por las mordidas de
these three dogs
estos tres perros
recia that bit the wife
recia que mordo a la mujer
tamba ranos in the crime that has not
tamba ranos en el delito que no han
prospered due to interests of not losing
prosperado por intereses de no perder
work he is going to fall because his
trabajo va a caer porque se le escaparon
dogs escaped and they caused a stir in the
los chuchos y la liaron en el
neighborhood nobody talks about falling or
vecindario es que nadie habla de caer o
not falling I remember as if it were yesterday I
no caer me acuerdo como si fuera ayer
was at my cousin's house and he
que estaba en la casa de mi primo y él
has a pitbull that I have known since it was a
tiene un pitbull que yo conocida desde
puppy and from one moment to the next it came and
cachorro y de un momento a otro vino y
bit me they had to call me
me mordió me tuvieron que poner como
four
cuatro
points Sure
puntos Claro
sure but listen to me nobody talks about falling
claro pero escúchame nadie habla de caer
or not falling they talk about something that has
o no caer se habla de una cosa que ha
happened I mean but this is like what does it
pasado o sea pero esto es como si que
have to do with whether it falls or not it won't
tiene que ver que caiga o no caiga no va
fall But well but this is
a caer Pero bueno pero esto es
strong obviously the dogs were
fuerte obviamente los perros fueron
removed from the neighborhood this has been
retirados del barrio esto se le ha
invented for sure eh And cosu found out
inventado d seguro eh Y cosu se enteró
because the guard fell with the three
porque la guardia cayó con los tres
dogs almost muzzled to tell him your
perros casi amordazados a decirle tus
dogs got loose all
perros se soltaron acaba de pasar todo
this just happened and cosu was sleeping
esto y cosu estaba durmiendo
perfect of what Frank says that if you
la perfecto de lo que dice Frank que si
are unbalanced your dogs will be
eres un desequilibrado tus perros serán
unbalanced I don't care it doesn't help
desequilibrados no me caro no ayuda
no but apart from that look You if you are
no pero aparte que fíjate Tú si eres
irresponsible that you have those dogs I mean
irresponsable que tienes esos perros o
the fact itself eh of course this will be
sea ya el hecho en sí eh claro esto lo
criminally condemned I don't know what
van a condenar penalmente yo no sé cómo
the law will be like in Argentina I don't know what
será la ley en Argentina no sé cuál será
the sentence will be but they will condemn him Yes
la condena pero que lo van a condenar Sí
or yes I mean this is because of IB this is because they
o sí o sea esto es por IB esto es porque
want to unite IB surely okay but
quieren unir IB seguramente vale pero
look at you already the
fíjate tú ya la la
irresponsibility that you have those
irresponsabilidad de que tienes esos
dogs but the dogs escape I
perros pero los perros se te escapan o
mean having those dogs you have left the
sea teniendo esos perros has dejado la
possibility of  that they
posibilidad de que se
escape danger
escapen peligr
still of course he's going to have to pay in
ahun claro va a tener que pagar en
fact they're going to start a
realidad le van a iniciar una acción
civil action against him because he's civilly liable for
civil porque él es responsable civil por
the dogs not criminally he doesn't have
los perroso no penal no tiene una
criminal liability for the dogs
responsabilidad penal por los perroso
well but if a dog ends up killing
bueno pero si un perro termina matando a
someone as well civil Of course but how do you
alguien como bueno civil Claro pero cómo
do it but they are dangerous dogs How does it
haces pero son perros peligrosos Cómo
happen p and a bulldog and well tremendously happens
pasa p y un dogo y bueno tremendo pasa
that Ah there is a responsibility to
que Ah hay una responsabilidad de
register it to have the muzzle to have
registrarlo de tener el bzal de tener
the vaccinations to have it registered there is
las vacunas de tenerlo registrado hay
a civil or
una responsabilidad civil o
contraventional liability but not criminal well H
contravencional pero no penal bueno H
a Revolution in the neighborhood because more I mean
una Revolución en el barrio porque más O
not criminal he says not
sea que no penal dice que no
criminal I don't know or I mean I don't know to what
penal no sé yo o sea no sé yo hasta qué
extent eh
punto eh
ehon to tell that obviously there were
ehon a contar que obviamente hubieron
other eh there were other incidents with these
otros eh hbi otros incidentes con estos
these three dogs and that well Obviously
estos tres perros y que bueno Obviamente
ccu that Llama Martín eh di salvo should have
ccu que Llama Martín eh di salvo debería
been responsible for this issue and
haber sido responsable con este tema y
therefore now they have just reported it
Por ende ahora lo lo acaban de denunciar
this is the last moment it was now
esto es el último momento fue ahora
terrible terrible because apart from that they
terrible terrible porque aparte le
can end up taking the dogs away from him the
pueden llegar a sacar los perros los
dogs in the neighborhood they have already taken them
perros del barrio ya se los
away I send a kiss to Carla who
retiraron le mando un beso a Carla que
was not in elementary school I mean no no I don't
no era de primario O sea que no no no la
see her very much  that's it Ah so the
veo muchísimo eso est Ah o sea que la
girl was or rather the victim the owner
chica era o sea la la víctima la dueña
of the dogs that also
de los perros que además la han
bit her who also
mordido que además la han
bit her is a friend of the
mordido es amiga de la de de la
presenter but come on
presentadora pero vamos
m the thing about it not being a
m eso de que no sea
crime that it's not a crime I have it's that I do
penal eso de que no sea penal tengo yo
n't know because of course Argentina I don't
es que no sé porque claro Argentina no
know how it will go the
sé cómo irá la
truth But the fact that you have
verdad Pero el hecho de que tú tengas
those dogs if they
esos perros se te
escape I don't know the
escapen No lo sé la
truth is she's going to pay for the
verdad va a pagar por los
damages the Argentine Dogo and the Canary have
daños el dogo argentino y el canario son
560 pci of jaw power it's
de 560 pci de potencia en mandíbula es
crazy
locura
here they would run the risk of being
aquí correrían el riesgo de ser
sacrificed and
sacrificados y
everything in Argentina it's not a
todo en Argentina no es
crime but I think that cocu now the
penal pero yo creo que eso cocu ahora se
fight is at the evening And if she wins the evening
pelea en la velada Y si gana la velada
you're right read the complaint Javi Let's
tienes la razón lee la denuncia Javi A
see let's
ver vamos a
look for it Let's
buscarla
see let's look for the complaint I
ver vamos a buscar la denuncia
was looking at photos of the complaint
que estaba viendo fotos de la denuncia
Allow me to doubt that if your dog ends
Permíteme dudar que si tu perro acaba
the life of another person they won't
con la vida de otra persona no te
charge you with reckless homicide at the
imputen un homicidio imprudente como
very least and if it's a ppp it's surely aggravating
poco y si es un ppp seguro es agravante
in Spain at least It should be like that
en España por lo menos Debería ser así
fortunately your Tyrion must be a good
afortunadamente tu tyrion debe ser buen
dog and  It doesn't give you any trouble
perro y no te da disgustos
No man you have seen a c that is not the
No hombre hab veis un c que no es lo
same you don't
mismo no
have three dogs that you choose from that
tienes tres perros que eliges de ese
profile so unbalanced that they
perfil tan desequilibrados que se
escape directly to attack the
escapan directamente a atacar la
negligence for me only confirms the
negligencia para mí solo confirma el
profile of
perfil de
coscu that the declarant was walking
coscu que la dicente estaba paseando a
her dog inside the private neighborhood Santa
su perra dentro del barrio privado Santa
Barbara and was near lot
Bárbara y había cerca del lote
400 when she was attacked by three dogs
400 cuando fue atacada por tres Canes
who threw her to the ground where the
quienes la arrojaron al suelo donde la
declarant avoided the attack of these
dicente se atajó del ataque que de estos
extremely aggressive animals biting her
animales sumamente agresivos mordiéndole
right arm causing
el brazo derecho ocasionándole
injuries to parts of the
lesiones en partes del
body that this type of breed is
cuerpo que este tipo de raza está
prohibited by regulations of the
prohibido estar por reglamento del
Santa Barbara neighborhood that these dogs
barrio Santa Bárbara que estos perros
learned
supo
later that they were breeds two of
después que se trataban de razas dos de
them pitbull While the last one does not
ellos pitbull Mientras que el último no
know But it was quite
sabe Pero era bastante
robust then they attacked in a very ta ta ta ta way
robusto luego atacaron de manera muy ta
the
ta ta ta tal al
good dog that killed the dog is
perro bueno que mató al perro vale
also worth the other that the aggression of
también de la otra que la agresión de
these animals ceased with the help of the
estos animales cesó por la ayuda de los
neighbors and the guard of the place who
vecinos y la guardia del lugar quienes
assisted the victim and transferred her
asistieron a la víctima y la trasladaron
to the veterinary clinic tat
a la clínica veterinaria tat
ta that the owner of the animals is called
ta que el dueño de los animales se llama
Martín Pérez and except for who lives  in
Martín Pérez y salvo quien vive en el
lot
lote
400 it is recorded that when
400 se deja constancia que al ser
Gabrielo was asked, thank you very much for
consultado gabrielo Muchas gracias por
the five members, a hug
los cinco miembros un abrazo
Rey, the person appearing about his
Rey el compareciente acerca de sus
intentions to intervene in the
intenciones de intervenir en el
process, he stated that
proceso expuso que
yes, when
sí que preguntada Sia la penal Sí o sea
asked if the criminal case is Yes, that is, it is criminal, when asked if the criminal facility refers that
que preguntada si instalación penal
yes, it is criminal, it is criminal, that everything he has to say, not being for more, was terminated on the spot, it is criminal, it is criminal, it is criminal, my goodness, a kiss ...
generalizado o sea yo sí que he notado
of the day also will
los temas y demás no del día también
not luare the rest of things that more
no luare el resto de cosas que más
put Put them for the news that I had not
puesto Mételas para el noticiero que no
realized king that below you
me había dado cuenta rey que abajo me
had put screenshots and
habías metido capturas y
such Javier pulsito mentioned you in the
demás Javier pulsito te mencionó en el
ibai live Why what have I done already
directo de ibai Por qué qu he hecho ya
now well by cto I was talking to
ahora bueno por cto estuve hablando con
him on
él por
WhatsApp this morning I have to
WhatsApp esta mañana le tengo que
answer him today I am terrible eh what did he
contestar hoy estoy fatal eh qué es lo
say spursito can you send it to me
que dijo spursito me lo podéis mandar
Javi goes and mentioned you But
Javi va y te mencionó Pero por
why And to me why have I done I have not
qué Y a mí por qué yo hecho yo no he
done anything this
hecho nada esta
week let's see let's see while they
semana a ver vamos a ver de mientras que
send it to me what Abi said that
me lo mandan lo que ha dicho Abi que por
apparently Jai has started to criticize
lo visto Jai se ha puesto a criticar a
the false caa the false ones of Twitch
los falsos caa a los falsos de Twitch
Javi you are better man better a
Javi ya estás mejor hombre mejor un
little better yes I am a little but I am still not
poco mejor si estoy un poco pero Sigo
well the truth is that I
sin estar bien la verdad es que me
feel bad [ __ ] the truth is that I
encuentro mal [__] la verdad es que me
feel
encuentro
weak and here is an exclusive
pocho y va una exclusiva
new day new cameo but it's a joke no I
nuevo día nuevo cameo pero es broma no O
mean But
sea Pero por
why do I imagine that there will be Sid some change
qué me imagino que habrá Sid algún cambo
of these jokes no eh of viewers
de estos de bromas no eh de espectadores
on Twitch Spain we have  burned out a lot
en Twitch España nos hemos quemado mucho
everyone if it is noticeable we are going down
todos si se nota vamos para abajo
hitting but the numbers are not
pegando pero los números no son
comparable to what there was before during
comparables a lo que había antes durante
the pandemic they are totally different times
la pandemia son otros tiempos totalmente
but in Spain you see people who normally
pero en España ves gente que normalmente
had 100,000 viewers who do not reach 28 or
tenía 100000 viewers que no llega a 28 o
30 eh People who had Well at the time
30 eh Peña que tenía Pues en su momento
5000 viewers with 800 or something like that nothing happens I
5000 viewers con 800 oa que no pasa nada
say again is that I think we are not
vuelvo a decir es que creo que no somos
aware of what it costs to have 800
conscientes de lo que cuesta tener 800
viewers especially nowadays it
viewers sobre todo hoy día al día me
occurs to me that in Spain we do not reach we do not
llega que en España no llegamos no
reach anything but nobody I mean it
llegamos a nada pero nadie quiero decir
is all down but the
es que está todo para abajo pero el
bulk of
groso de
everyone down but down hitting each
todos abajo pero para abajo pegándose
other brutally it is the fault of the rise of
una [__] brutal es culpa de auge de
the Latinos It is that the quality of the
los latinos Es que la calidad de los
Spanish has dropped I think it is a little I think there are
españoles ha bajado creo que es un poco
three things
creo que hay tres cosas
here is that
aquí es que
also what I tell you I mean what could it be due to Well
también qué te digo O sea a qué se puede
because there are more and more
deber Pues a que cada vez hay más
then if there are more and more then
entonces si cada vez hay más pues se
people are divided and if nobody I mean in the
divide la gente y si nadie o sea al
end the viewers go to the one who
final los espectadores se lo lleva el
strengthens their audience the most I am not the one who creates
que más afiance su audiencia El que crea
community
comunidad
the only one who associates those and so many
no soy el único que asocia esos y tantos
dogs with a way of trying to
perros a una forma de tratar de
show themselves as more macho badass bar let's
mostrarse como más macho barra
see let's see for me they are dogs a little bit of a
ver a ver para mí son perros un poco
joke it's not that you make me
[__] es que no es que me hacéis
throw they are a little bit
tirar son un poco
chauvinistic having those dogs is a little bit chauvinistic well
canis tener esos perros es un poco canis
no because I know people who are
bueno no porque yo conozco a gente que
not chauvinistic no let's see I am more of a
no es canis no a ver yo soy más de un
Coque a Coque a dog that you a dog that you
Coque un Coque un perro que tú un perro
can a dog that you hug a
que tú puedas un perro que tú abraces un
dog that you know what I know something else another
perro que sabes lo que sé otra cosa otro
type for me the pet of another style it is
tipo para mí la mascota de otro estilo
because the content is always the
se debe a que el contenido siempre es el
same and people get tired of course and
mismo y la gente se cansa claro y van
new things keep coming out and that's it Hey
saliendo cosas nuevas y ya está Oye
find me that cameo please I want to see it let's
buscarme ese cameo porfa que lo quiero
see what it is
ver a ver a qué se
due to let's see is that in the end playing
debe a ver es que al final jugando a
video games and doing those things
videojuegos y haciendo esas cosas
no Mariana from 40,000 to 20,000 Sprint from
no Mariana de 40.000 a 20.000 Sprint de
70,000 to 20,000 Juan from 30,000 to 10,000
70.000 a 20.000 Juan de 30.000 a 10.000
everyone has gone
todos han
down I think it depends on the times
bajado yo creo que depende de las épocas
of the topics more and more  channels
de los temas de cada vez más canales
to choose from there are times of the day when you
para elegir que hay momentos del día en
want to do something other than
que apetece más hacer otra cosa que
watch people play video games we don't have
mirar gente jugar videojuegos no tenemos
house arrest measures in effect a
medidas de arresto domiciliario en vigor
whole cocktail for the
todo un cóctel para que los canales
big channels to see their numbers reduced even
grandes vean sus números reducidos hasta
on TV they
en la tele lo
notice it but let's see for example there are
notan pero a ver yo por ejemplo hay veas
days last week there was a day
hay días la semana pasada hubo un día
that we had 7000 viewers there was another
que tuvimos 7000 espectadores hubo otro
that we had 6000 on telesalseo there was a day that we
que tuvimos 6000 en telesalseo hubo un
had 5000 and then there was another
día que tuvimos 5000 y luego hubo otro
that we had
que tuvimos
2000 today on telesalseo I don't think we have
2000 hoy en telesalseo creo que no hemos
200 now however here where
200 ahora sin embargo aquí que
we are normally 2000 today there are
normalmente somos 2000 Hoy hay
2500 I don't know I think it depends it doesn't
2500 No sé yo creo que depende no
depend on the day it depends on the subject it depends on
depende el día depende el tema depende
the time it depends on who else is there the
la hora depende quién más esté los
kids who watch them are already 25 and if they
niñatos que les veyan ya tienen 25 y si
don't get involved in political issues controversy
no se mojan en tema política polémica
etcetera they are not interested there is the fan of
etcétera no interesan está el fand de
sick people and little
enfermitos y poco
else the gossip is not governed by the same
más el salseo no se rige por las mismas
rules Well of course the gossip is
reglas Bueno claro el salseo es
different of course I do
diferente
n't know the truth is there are many
claro No sé la verdad son muchos
factors it is difficult to stay
factores cuesta mucho mantenerse
also the first one has burned out a lot
también la primera se ha quemado mucho
here in Spain we have all burned out a lot,
aquí en España nos hemos quemado mucho
a little [ __ ] for the 10
todos un poas la zoi [__] por los 10
months Thank you very much you are going to have to
meses Muchas gracias van a tener que
get a real job and you a good
conseguir trabajo de verdad y tú un buen
hobby so you don't waste your time
Hobby para no estar perdiendo tu tiempo
in chats Daniel then each one of you can
en los chats Daniel entonces cada uno
go find your own way then no
que se vaya buscando la vida entonces no
my love little and it shows I think that Friday
mi amor poco y se nota creo que el vier
has also burned us out he has been seeing us for
también nos ha quemado nos lleva viendo
like maybe 3 years if now someone comes out
como a lo mejor 3 años si ahora sale
Well from Latin America new that
alguien Pues de latinoamérica nueva que
finds funny or whatever well it is the
le haga gracia o lo que sea pues es la
novelty I mean I have been streaming for 6 years
novedad quiero decir yo llevo 6 años en
the rest of my colleagues are
streaming el resto de mis compañeros
similar I mean they are the same [ __ ]
parecido o sea son las mismas [__]
faces for years people are
caras an años la gente está hasta la
fed up with us you know what we
puella de nosotros sabes más no nos
are not getting together to do the big thing
estamos juntando para hacer la gran cosa
for the reason one because we are fed up with each
por el motivo uno porque estamos hasta
other more than at the
la poa unos e otros más que en su
time the Stream in Latin America for whatever
momento el Stream en Latinoamérica por
reasons well it was not so well
los motivos que fuese pues no era tan
known or there were not so many in
tan conocido o no había tantos en
Latin America so everything that we
latinoameric entonces todo lo que
were experiencing they are
estuvimos experimentando lo están
experiencing now then I mean the
experimentando ahora entonces O sea la
Latin American community has one
comunidad latinoamericana tiene una cosa
really good thing and it is Peña faithful to the max it
buenísima y es Peña fiel a más no poder
is as if they go to if their own people
es como que si se van a si los suyos
come out  they're going to go their own way and
e salen se van a ir a los suyos y nos
kick us in the ass I
van a pegar una patada en el culo me
think it's great Eh so that's what's
parece genial Eh entonces es lo que está
happening also eh the main problem
pasando también eh el principal problema
with many streamers is that they
de muchos streamers es pes que hacen
all make the same shitty content it
todos hacen la misma [__] de contenido
seems to me that it's simply
a mí me parece que eso es simplemente
because of your tastes I mean you think that for
por tus gustos O sea tú piensas que para
you watching that content you don't like but there are
ti ver ese content no te gusta pero hay
a lot of people for whom that's what they look for I mean there are a
mucha gente que es lo que lo que busca o
lot of people who stay in the
sea hay mucha gente que se pone en los
background of streams there are a lot of people who don't
streams de fondo hay mucha gente que no
look to watch content like the one that's not a [ __ ] fool
busca ponerse un content tipo el de ni
or the one that's a joke or the one that you know
lo jeda o el de guaña o el de sabes
Twitch has always been something to put on
Twitch siempre ha sido algo para ponerte
in the background etcetera
de fondo etcétera
But it's like for example criticizing the
Pero es como por ejemplo criticar los ya
chatting or criticizing the
chatting o criticar las
eh reactions as is from the outside it looks
eh reacciones tal cual desde fuera se ve
repetitive and it's a [ __ ] pain but
como repetitivo y es un [__] [__] pero
from the inside it's what gives the most numbers and
desde dentro es lo que más números da y
if it's what gives the most numbers it's because it's what people like the most
si es lo que más números da es porque es
but sometimes it's what is
lo que más gusta pero c vez es lo que
criticized the most because it's what is
más se critica porque es lo que más se
seen the most I really think that it's all that
ve Yo realmente creo que es todo que han
new powers have appeared in
aparecido nuevas potencias en
Latin America that weren't there before It's
Latinoamérica que antes no estaban Es
logical that then the living ones  they
lógico que entonces los vivos se se
share Hello to Hello cu months BB eh And
reparten Hola a Hola cu meses BB eh Y
all the [ __ ] from the time that we've
todo el la [__] de de época que
been carrying around all the [ __ ] that
llevamos atrás todo toda la [__] que
has come out day after day after day that has
ha salido un día tras otro tras otro que
n't burned alone I have another theory
no ha quemado solo yo tengo otra teoría
too Look they also do a lot
también Mira ellos también hacen mucho
of collaborations eh
lo de las colaboraciones eh
in fact on many occasions we have
de hecho en muchas ocasiones hemos
commented that they do collaborations with
comentado que hacen colaboraciones con
people that they can't see or I mean I've already
gente entre s que no se pueden ver o sea
explained this a million
esto ya lo he explicado un millón de
times no I'm not going to explain it again
veces no no voy a volver a explicarlo
okay the collaborations no And now you
vale las colaboraciones no Y ahora te
see
ves a
x collaborating with y or you see let's
un x colaborando con y o te ves a vamos
see you only have to collaborate
a ver tú solamente tienes que colaborar
you have to dedicate yourself to your thing okay And you
tú tienes que dedicarte a lo tuyo vale Y
have to dedicate yourself to your thing and that's it
te tienes que dedicar a lo tuyo y punto
and you only have to collaborate with the
y solamente tienes que colaborar con la
people that you fully trust you
gente que son de tu plena confianza
know with whom you feel comfortable with
sabes con los que te sientes a gusto con
those who are not there out of interest
los que no están por el interés
Okay what happens if you do those
Vale qué es lo que pasa si tú haces esas
collaborations imagine I'm going to give a
colaboraciones imagínate voy a poner un
random example imagine Juan Guarnizo
ejemplo al azar imagínate Juan guarnizo
with Gref Imagine that they can't
con gref Imagínate que entre ellos no se
really see each other But they are
pueden ver en verdad Pero están
collaborating because it's in the interest of the business
colaborando porque interesa el negocio
what is going to happen in  wait a minute
qué es lo que va a pasar en un momento
because in the end if you're going to go too far
pues que al final si os vais a pasar
followers okay And surely one will
seguidores vale Y seguramente uno le va
invite the other's series and the other the
a invitar la serie del otro y al otro
same despite the problems you
igual a pesar de los problemas que
have But there will come a time when you're
tengáis Pero va a llegar un momento en
both going to be streaming at the
el que Vais a estar streame los dos a la
same time So maybe followers that you
vez Entonces a lo mejor seguidores que
've gone too far Paolo a kiss maybe
os habéis pasado Paolo un beso a lo
followers that you've gone too far
mejor seguidores que habéis
Well the day that
pasado Pues el día que
gref in miini has to see someone
gref en miini tener que ver a alguien
play I'd better start playing at
jugar mejor me pongo yo a jugar en mi
home better podcast listen to stories I'll
casa mejor podcast oír historias os
tell you a kiss a kiss sorita Thank you very much
salseo un beso un beso sorita Muchas
What can happen Well
gracias Qué es lo que puede pasar Pues
look Imagine that Juan Guarnizo
mira Imagínate que Juan guarnizo
collaborates with gref they go too far followers
colabora con gref se pasan seguidores
But what happens is that now Juan
Pero qué es lo que pasa que ahora Juan
Guarn one day does something cooler pu
guarn un día hace una cosa más chula pu
the viewers and gre is live
los espectadores y gre está en directo
Well gre's viewers are going to go
Pues los espectadores de gre se van a ir
see juarniso
a ver a juarniso
be his followers so he sends
sea seguidores a él para que él te manda
you but in the end there will be a day that it
a ti pero al final va a haber día que te
will harm you because he will take
va a perjudicar porque se va a llevar
yours but I'll make it worse for you
los tuyo pero es que te lo pongo peor
gref collaborates with Juan  guarnizo passes
gref colabora con Juan guarnizo se pasan
followers but the following month
seguidores pero es que al mes siguiente
Juan guarnizo collaborates with the
Juan guarnizo colabora con el
Dead, he passes followers to the
Dead le pasa seguidores al
Dead Well now the Dead Imagine that he
Dead Pues ahora el Dead Imagínate que
does something that is great Well
hace una cosa que es la [__] Bueno pues
now you
ahora tú
indirectly are going to lose followed
indirectamente vas a perder seguido
seges or you go no followers they follow you they
seges o vas no seguidores te siguen te
follow you but as long as the other one is
siguen pero mientras que esté el otro
doing something cooler they are going to see the
haciendo una cosa más chula van a ver al
others instead of you dude no no don't
otros en vez de aí tío no no no hagáis
meet anyone I haven't collaborated with anyone who
conocido a nadie no colaboré con nadie
is not yours so they are not
que no sean de los vuestros que no te
going to get you in then you know what I'm
vayan a meter luego sabes lo que te
telling you that too that's also what it has to do
digo eso también eso también es lo que
as they all collaborate with each
tiene que como van colabor todos entre
other and doing things then in the end the
ellos y haciendo cosas pues al final la
audience is divided more I mean and then there's
audiencia la dividen más O sea y luego
the other factor the other factor is
está el otro factor el otro factor es
that
que
you there are people there are people who are
tú que hay gente que hay gente que está
here for their talent and because they
aquí por su talento y porque
have character and the character of a leader to
tiene carácter y carácter de líder de
lead and to lead an audience and to
liderar y de llevar una audiencia y de
present and to communicate and then there are
presentar y de comunicar y luego están
those who are around okay I mean those
los que están alrededor vale o sea los
around are simply
que están alrededor simplemente son
known for being the one who accompanies this
conocidos por ser el que acompaña este
for example for me personally an
por ejemplo para mí personalmente una
aoer unaer that is neither fish nor
aoer unaer eso no tiene ni chicha ni
fowl that is what it has  that's a
limonada eso está que qué tiene eso un
karches carch please I mean a carch
karches carch por favor O sea un carch
is the typical person that you can
es la típica persona que puedes
hire to put it here in the public
contratar para ponerlo aquí de público
I applauded and stuff but if it happens to
aplaudí y esas cosas pero si me pasa a
me sometimes I have the least three
mí que a veces tengo el menor que tres
game between the channels that I follow and I don't
partido entre los canales que sigo y no
know which one to go to directly and in the end I have to
sé a qué directo meterme y al final
consume almost everything in
tengo que consumir casi todo en
deferred clear people are divided but
diferido claro la gente se divide pero
then there are some who are a Comanche
luego hay algunos que son un Comanche
when they caught the grace with El
cuando cogieron la gracia con El
Comanche without having anything against Comanche
Comanche sin tener nada contra Comanche
but Comanche I mean there are people who are
pero Comanche O sea hay gente que son
by themselves they handle the content and
por ellos mismos manejan el contenido y
then there are those who are known for
luego están los que son conocidos por
being companions or participants in
ser acompañantes de o participantes de
the series of a
las series d un
Focus or so
Focus o sea por
please And that is also what is
favor Y eso también es lo que
noticed by the people who have suffered it
notan a las personas que lo han sufrido
whether because they are guilty or because of
ya sea por culpables o por daños
collateral damage but to the viewer and not only
colaterales sino al espectador y no solo
the viewer who no longer wants to see it
al espectador que ya no lo quiere ver
because he does not agree with what has
porque no está de acuerdo con lo que ha
happened but to the one who simply wants to
pasado sino al que ya simplemente quiere
get away because he has realized that
alejarse porque se ha dado cuenta de que
you get into Twitch to pass the
tú te metes a Twitch para pasar el
time to pass the time not To have
tiempo para pasar el rato no Para haber
problems not to see horrible things no To
problemas no para ver cosas horribles no
have confrontation you get involved  to
Para haber enfrentacion tú te metes a
Twitch to burn time if you
Twitch para quemar el tiempo si lo
think about the subject I saw the smartest has
piensas con el tema vi el más listo ha
been I has put together two projects that
sido I se ha montado dos proyectos que
are co poros that every time they play
son co poros que cada vez que juegan
has between 60 and 100k or even more in
tiene entre 60 y 100k o incluso más en
important matches to make content let's
partidos importantes pu hacer contenido
see the smartest do not pani What is it if
a ver el más listo no te pani Qué es si
I do that with 1000 viewers
yo hago eso con 1000 viewers lo hace
Carlos does it with 600 or Pau does it with 300
Carlos con 600 o lo hace Pau con 300
well believe me 60 or 100,000 viewers
pues créeme que 60 o 100,000 viewers
is to blame short content is
tiene la culpa contenido corto gusta
more popular there is also that factor that is now
más también está ese factor que ahora
like very fashionable that of Yes yes it is
está como muy de moda eso de Sí sí es
true there are more platforms
verdad hay más plataformas contenido
short content Yes yes let's see what the
corto Sí sí a ver cuál es el
cameo is that is true dude no no
cameo eso es verdad tío no no
noos Juan what are these tweets about or can't you
noos Juan a qué vienen estos tweets o no
touch the subject I don't know it's that I just
se puede tocar el tema no lo sé es que
read like a tweet thread of yours
acabo de leer como un hilo de tweet suyo
goes for a I think eh it's that I don't understand
va por un creo eh es que no me me entero
things and I read it just now it's that
de las cosas y lo he leído justo ahora
I don't those rolls I think it's a
es que yo no esos rollos creo que es un
what the hell did you do to your hair
qué [__] te has hecho en el pelo
pulse
pulsito
dude what did you do in the  hair What
cabrón qué te has hecho en el pelo Qué
happened to you? One got mad at a
te ha pasado una se ha enfadado con una
tiktoker with Jerry maybe or something like that
tiktoker con Jerry puede ser o algo así
[ __ ] This is me, don't get out get out get out of there Get out of
[__] Este soy yo no sal sal sal sal de
there what are you saying dude
ahí Sal de ahí qué estáis diciendo tío t
no no no don't put the God dude what are you
no no no metéis el Dios tío qué estáis
talking about I love it I love it because you don't like to
hablando Me encanta me encanta porque no
talk about somewhat
os gusta nada hablar de temas un poco
thorny issues that that that I don't give a damn or
espinosos que que que que me la pela o
rather let's talk or rather I don't know what the
sea hablemos o sea no sé de qué va el
issue is about who the [ __ ] is Jerry yes Jerry
tema quién [__] es Jerry si Jerry
I think it's you Jerry me too me
Pienso que eres tú Jerry yo tamb yo
too but I said a tiktoker I'm neither a
también pero he dicho una tiktoker No
nor a tiktoker So it's not
soy ni una ni tiktoker O sea que no soy
me but we have to see it later in length No well
yo per hay que verlo luego en largo No
I'm not either Well I'm not either well then that's it let's
pues yo tampoco soy Pues yo tampoco soy
not talk that's it that's it
pues entonces ya está no hablemos ya
next no but let Juani come in and
siguiente no pero que entre Juani y lo
tell it No but what are we
cuente No pero qué somos
now save me from Oliveira Oliveira
ahora el sálvame del oliveira oliveira
I am
soy
and if you are a man woman or child or adult
e si seas hombre mujer o niño o adulto
if I mess with you Answer me don't
si me meto contigo Respóndeme a mí no
involve my family [ __ ] That has
involucres a mi familia [__] Ese ha
been the way I mean they have mentioned me
sido el camino O sea me han mencionado
with
con
Piqué but whistle Why  you get me into
Piqué pero [__] Por qué me metes en
this mess I mean they mentioned me with
estos líos O sea me han mencionado con
Piqué Hey
Piqué Oye pues
look and Piqué and Piqué must have said that
mira y Piqué y Piqué habrá dicho el
bastard Javier I will beira the bastard
cabrón de Javier I beira el cabrón de
Javier Iira a
Javier iira una
dick yv an exclusive conone
[__] yv una exclusiv conone
eh He's not going to give it to him yv has known how to manage
eh No le va a dar yv ha sabido gestionar
what he's had to have it until he
lo que ha tenido por tenerlo hasta
got there he has worked very hard And such
llegar ahí ha trabajado muy duro Y tal
But I don't think it's comparable or to say he
Pero no creo que sea comparable ni decir
's the smartest because everyone works
es el más listo porque cada uno funciona
under their possibilities and what he feels like
bajo sus posibilidades y lo que le de
also the head doesn't feel good
también la cabeza no se siente buen
Genuine because I
rollo Genuino porque a mí me gustan
really like collaborations collaborations
mucho las colaboraciones colaboraciones
and series to me for I mean imo the
y series a m para o sea imo las
collaborations are completely
colaboraciones están completamente
dead all the events and such I mean
muertas tod los eventos y tal o sea de
the events that give me the least laziness
los eventos que me dan menos pereza
could be the Twitch cap or things piqu
podría ser las Twitch cap o cosas piqu
you know for sure I don't think so I don't think so I don't think I see I don't know
te conoces seguro no
that maybe I don't
creo no creo ver no sé que a lo mejor no
know the truth I don't think it doesn't sound to me that
sé la verdad no creo no me suena que
I've had any clash with something it's that I haven't
haya yo tenido ningún cruce con algo es
even dealt with many
que ni siquiera he tratado muchos temas
piquet issues and anything like that
de piquet y nada por el
Javi I'm from tea salseo and the
estilo Javi soy de tes salseo y del
little one Thanks to my daughter I only watch
canijo Gracias a mi hija solo Veo la
TV to put you to  you A kiss
tele para ponerte a ti Un beso
Cristina yes they are very personal that
Cristina sí que son muy personales que
in the end it is the streams individually
al final es los streams individualmente
without having to because in the end an event
sin tener que porque al final un evento
with 100 people with the movements that there
con 100 personas con la de movidas que
are behind it only leads to
hay atrás sol lleva
falsehood, people who move for interest
falsedad gente que se mueve por interés
l Thank you very much, let's see one time I gave an
l Muchas gracias a ver una vez di una
exclusive that was Auron's response
exclusiva que fue la respuesta de auron
to Piqu when Piqu started saying like
a piqu cuando piqu se puso a decir como
[Music]
que
no like Pi started saying that Auron didn't
no como pi se puso a decir que auron no
want to no Or that they didn't want to Call
quiso no O que ellos no quisieron Llamar
Auron for the k Then send the
a auron para la k Enton mand la
answer that
respuesta esa
exclusive That that exclusive that
exclusiva Esa esa exclusiva esa
exclusive was good
exclusiva fue buena
eh That exclusive [ __ ] I don't know
eh Esa exclusiva [__] es que no sé por
why it's not expanded on me that exclusive was
qué no se me amplía esa exclusiva fue
powerful and didn't have much
potente y no tuvo mucha
impact and people that you know that you haven't
repercusión y gente que tú sabes que no
seen them insulting each other at another time
los has visto insultarse en otro momento
and then you see them talking as if nothing at
y luego los ves hablando como si nada a
the same time that those people if they are at
la vez que esa gente si se encuentra en
the event it gets totally uncomfortable Ju nobody
el evento se pone full incómodo Ju nadie
says how [ __ ] tiresome you know he does His
dice qué [__] cansino sabes hace Su
content which is playing [ __ ]
contenido que es jugar a [__]
video games talking about Maybe two
videojuegos hablar de A lo mejor dos
things and sitting in his [ __ ] in
cosas y estar sentado en su su [__] en
his [ __ ] room and nobody is going to say
su [__] habitación y nadie va a decir
that  it's boring What happens is that when people
eso aburre Qué pasa que cuando la gente
start to go up or down numbers is
empieza a subir a bajar números es
when you criticize with arguments that in your
cuando criticas con argumentos que en tu
head make sense But it's that
cabeza tienen sentido Pero es que
really in the end Many times they don't even
realmente al fin de cuentas Muchas veces
apply reality they are different I
ni se aplican la realidad son otra yo
think the reality is that the numbers go
creo que la realidad es que los números
down because we come from quarantine and
bajan porque venimos de cuarentena y
obviously people are no longer as
obviamente la peña ya no está tan
connected and that after so much bad
conectada y que después de tanto mal
vibes there are a lot of people who have
rollo hay mucha gente que se ha
distanced themselves not streamers but
distanciado no streamers sino los
viewers there are a lot of people who have stopped
viewers hay mucha Peña que ha dejado de
watching x who have stopped watching Twitch in
ver a x que ha dejado de ver Twitch en
general because it does not provide them with the
general porque no le no le aporta la
tranquility and fun that they were
tranquilidad y y diversión que iba
looking for in the first instance when they
buscando en primera instancia cuando se
got into Twitch for the first time if you
metió a Twitch por primera vez de si
want different content it will
queréis contenido diferente va a dejar
stop being Twitch content because
de ser contenido de Twitch porque el
overly prepared content is
contenido preparado en exceso es
content of television things more
contenido de cosas televisivas cosas más
scripted things more things and there we go back to the
guionizadas cosas más y ahí volvemos al
beginning the essence of Twitch is lost
principio se pierde la esencia de Twitch
and that is what we later criticize ibai for
y es lo que luego le criticamos a ibai
not that he is bringing television to such and such
no de que está trayendo la tele a a tal
if you want something more prepared Go to
si quieres algo más preparado Vete a
YouTube because Twitch is what it
YouTube porque es que Twitch es lo que
can offer you it is not from many
te puede brindar no es de muchos
influencers but there is too much
influencers sino que hay demasiado
audience Because if there is  many many people
público Porque si hay muchos mucha gente
trying to make content but there isn't
que intenta hacer contenido pero no hay
that much public there aren't that many influencers
tanto público no hay tantos influencers
The problem is that there are too many people
El problema es que hay demasiada gente
on social media and on top of that we come from this whole
en redes y encima venimos de toda esta
wave of hate that I think was very
ola de odio que yo creo que fue muy
driven as well but I think people do
impulsada también pero esto la gente
n't even realize it was very
creo que ni se da cuenta fue muy
driven by eh the quarantine I
impulsada por eh la cuarentena la yo
think the quarantine has left
creo que la cuarentena ha dejado taras y
many people with psychological problems and issues and it has
problemas psicológicos a mucha gente y
also given them very
también les ha dado costumbres muy
toxic habits and on social media it says their today you had 2
tóxicas y en redes dice sus hoy tenías 2
on telesalseo yes today there were very few of us
en telesalseo sí hoy éramos muy poquillo
No Susi on telesalseo
No Susi en telesalseo
today there were very few of us on telesalseo
hoy éramos poquillo en telesalseo
that to this day they haven't been able to
que a día de hoy no se los han podido
take them away from you it's that the things that
quitar a ti es que las cosas que está
Abi is saying that if the quarantine we're going to
diciendo Abi que si la cuarentena vamos
see obviously
ver evidentemente
I really don't notice to see This
yo es que realmente no noto a ver Esto
is something like it is talked about a lot not that
es algo como que se habla mucho no que
the quarantine gave like more audience to
la cuarentena dio como más audiencia a
all channels in general but then it
todos los canales en general pero luego
already
ya
went down I really will see not what I
bajó Yo es que realmente verá no lo yo
in my case I speak of my case eh I mean
en mi caso Yo hablo de mi caso eh o sea
I am that in my case no I would not know what to
yo es que en mi caso no No sabría qué
tell you It's that what happens is that the
decirte Es que lo que pasa es que el
social Blade does not mark you  the social
social Blade no te marca la el social
Blade does not mark you
Blade no te marca
How can you go back in the
la Cómo se puede volver atrás en el
social Blade is there a way to go back
social Blade hay forma de Volver atrás
It's that today we wanted to see it I have not
Es que hoy lo queríamos ver yo no he
noticed a single Look if you notice
notado ni una Mira si os dais cuenta
this would be my my main channel okay
esto sería mi mi canal principal vale
mm this I don't know what the [ __ ] I would delete 7
mm esto no sé qué [__] borraría yo 7
million visits here I don't know what the [ __ ]
millones aquí de visita no sé qué [__]
I would delete in
es lo que borraría yo en el
2021 I have no [ __ ] idea what
2021 no tengo ni [__] idea de lo que
2021 But well The Movida I always
2021 Pero bueno La Movida Yo siempre me
keep more or less the same my
mantengo más o menos los mism mis
numbers from time to time there is a
números de vez en cuando hay una época
special time Look
especial Mira
this May June 2022 Jai wake up you're
esta mayo junio 2022 Jai espabila que te
going to sleep live well I just got
vas a dormir en directo pues me acabo de
up n it's that I'm sick
levantarse n es que estoy malito
forgive me Jos I'm sick I would need I would
perdonadme Jos estoy malito necesitaría
need I don't know 3000 members or
necesitaría yo que sé 3000 miembros o
something okay in your case no but in many
algo vale en tu caso no pero en de los
others yes the quarantine marked
otros muchos sí la cuarentena marcó
a lot of audiences went up yes I
subieron muchas audiencias sí Yo
understand that let's see I understand that by
entiendo que a ver yo entiendo que por
logic already but come on it's
lógica ya pero vamos es
not by logic in quarantine
no por lógica en la cuarentena estaba
the entire planet was locked up Well there would be
todo el planeta encerrado Pues habría
more consumption of course that's  logical too
más consumo claro eso Es lógico también
but I imagine it will be
pero me imagino que será para
depending on what for depending on what
dependiendo que para dependiendo qué qué
content but for me my audience
contenidos pero yo para mí mi audiencia
you know what I'm telling you Look I always
sabes lo que te digo Mira siempre me
stay there this is the main channel
mantengo ahí esto es el canal principal
okay This peak of 5 million visits
vale Este pico de 5 millones de visita
if I'm not mistaken this This is
si no me equivoco esto Esto es lo de
Johnny dep okay
Johnny dep vale
then then over here there are a few months that I
luego luego por aquí hay unos meses que
had the channel abandoned if I'm not
tuve el canal abandonado si no me
mistaken over here you see that it is with
equivoco por aquí lo veis que está con
a million this is with the channel stopped
un millón esto es con el canal parado
that I didn't only do telesalseo and
que no me solamente hacía telesalseo y
the canijo and then over
el canijo y luego por
here last month no no the previous one
aquí el mes pasado no no el anterior el
last month three Let's see another one
mes pasado tres A ver vamos a ver otro
let's see
vamos a ver
canijo that I think is where
canijo que yo creo que es donde más
I spend the most time
tiempo estoy
no let's
no a
see it always moves Look it always
ver siempre se mueve Mira siempre se
moves between 3 million 2
mueve entre los 3 millones 2
cu
cu
okay here there was a month of 14 million
vale aquí hubo un mes de 14 millones de
visits I don't know what month it would be the
visitas no sé qué mes sería la
truth it seems that it is the
verdad tiene toda la pinta que es el
same month as Johnny what happens that
mismo mes de Johnny de lo que pasa que
in the canijo I didn't try Johnny de
en el canijo yo no trataba Johnny de
So I don't know what it is but
Entonces no sé qué es lo que es pero
well Look 6 7
bueno Mira 6 7
million 8 million over here one month
millones 8 millones por aquí un mes
then over here another
luego por aquí otros
eight the last months it has gone up I don't know
ocho los últimos meses ha subido no sé
the truth is I have no idea the
la verdad es que no tengo ni idea la
truth I wouldn't know what to tell you the
verdad No sabría qué deciros la
truth that it has left you with some problems for
verdad que te ha dejado algún problema a
me No because I spent the quarantine
mí No porque yo la cuarentena la pasé
divinely well divinely no I
divinamente bueno divinamente no se me
lost it a little but the moment Javi You
fue un poco la ella pero el momento Javi
didn't take advantage of the pandemic or
No aprovechaste la pandemia ni el
Auron's candy what
caramelito de auron qué
candy what Auron's candy I didn't
caramelito qué caramelito de auron no
take advantage I was able to go out on the street it
aproveché ya pude salir a la calle se me
passed me by the trajectory of artists is
pasó la trayectoria de los artistas
usually always the same when they have a
suele ser siempre Igual cuando tienen un
peak like that suddenly here and then Pam
pico así de repente p acá y ya luego Pam
But this is due to this when something
Pero esto se debe a esto cuando algo
is very well received then it has
tiene muy buen recibimiento luego tiene
a lot of criticism because there are many people who
mucha crítica porque hay mucha gente que
when everything is beautiful nobody
que que cuando todo es bonito nadie
talks but at the time
habla pero a la que ya está empezando la
people are starting to say things everyone
gente a decir cosas ya todo el mundo
talks and also many people who had
habla y también mucha gente que tenía
a lot of hype here but then when they
mucho hype aquí pero luego cuando ya se
have gotten used to it then they don't feel like it
ha acostumbrado pues ya no le apetece
as much and well people leave people
tanto y pues gente que se va gente que
come but here you are left with semi
viene pero aquí ya te queda semit
toxicity and semi beautiful things at the
toxicidad y semic cosas bonitas al
beginning everything is beautiful and here it is usually
principio todo es bonito y aquí suele
all ugly at what point of the curve
ser todo feo en qué momento de la curva
are you if I had to apply this
estás tú si tuviese que aplicar yo esto
look I would  so I liked it liked it liked it
mira estaría así yo gustaba gustaba
and why don't I get Paint anymore
gustaba y porque no me da más el Paint
what dramas joke no but my case is
qué dramas bromita no pero yo mi caso es
exactly the same as mine First they love me a
exactamente el mío a mí Primero me aman
lot then they hate me a lot and then it
mucho luego me odian mucho y luego
starts all over again But the thing is that I've already
vuelta a empezar Pero es que yo esto ya
experienced this a few times when I
lo he vivido unas cuantas veces cuando
start with x person Everyone loves me a
empiezo con x persona Todos me aman
lot it ends with that person Everyone
mucho se acaba con esa persona Todos me
hates me a lot I mean she's saying I don't know if you
odian mucho o sea está diciendo no sé si
understood her the same way she says
la habéis entendido igual que yo dice
wait I'll repeat it again please This
espérate lo vuelvo a repetir por fa Esto
a kiss minani min nanami Listen to this
un beso minani min nanami Escuchar esto
Listen to this then they hate me a lot and
Escuchar esto luego me odian mucho y
then it starts all over again But the thing is that I've
luego vuelta a empezar Pero es que yo
already experienced this a few times
esto ya lo he vivido unas cuantas veces
when I start with x person Everyone
cuando empiezo con x persona Todos me
loves me a lot it ends with that person
aman mucho se acaba con esa persona
Everyone hates me a lot I mean her
Todos me odian mucho o sea sus ciclos
professional cycles depend on her
profesionales dependen de sus relaciones
romantic relationships I mean she's saying that her
amorosas o sea está diciendo que sus
cycles depend on the boyfriends she ends
ciclos depende de los novios que se va
up with when I start with someone everyone
echando cuando empiezo con alguien todos
loves me a lot and when I leave them everyone hates me
me aman mucho y cuando los dejo todos me
and now who have you left
y ahora a quién has dejado
you know when they have loved you
sabes cuándo te han amado
a lot they need a new boyfriend of course let's see
mucho necesitan nuevo novio claro a ver
careful carche eh careful carche
cuidado carche eh cuidado carche que
this can  be a hint eh And then it
esto puede ser una indirecta eh Y luego
settles down and then they
ya se establece y luego otra vez me
love me a lot again something happens and I
quieren un montón de nuevo pasa algo y
hate everyone But because she's
me odio a todo el mundo Pero porque está
admitting that her increases are because of
admitiendo que sus subidas son por
affairs she's saying it no in the end it
amoríos lo está diciendo no al final la
gives me a lot of cringe saying the phrase but it is it is
me da mucho cringe decir la frase pero
the reality it gives me a lot of cringe
es es la realidad da mucho cringe la
people function a lot in herds where
gente funciona mucho por rebaños dónde
Vicente goes where people go people They
va Vicente dónde va la gente la gente
seek social acceptance to be
Busca mucho la aceptación social formar
part of groups to say what they say HM to
parte de grupos decir lo que dicen HM
think that they are They have people by their side
pensar que están Tienen a gente al lado
which is completely false Because
cosa que es completamente falsa Porque
if you say how you really think or
si tú dices como piensas de verdad o
say something different they will kick
dices algo diferente te van a echar de
you out of there but in the meantime they are very calm they are chill there So when people love me they love me loudly but when people hate me they hate me loudly and that's it she interprets it like that in
así en
family she interprets it Like
familia ella lo interpreta
this I'm going to grab a redbull to see
Así voy a [__] un redbull para ver lo
Juan warn's thing I'm
de Juan warn soy
Ari
Ari
quio your body
quio tu cuerpo
m let's
m a
see what you're doing What are you doing let's
ver qué estáis
see I think I think we
a ver yo creo yo creo que este extracto
should start this extract with the cameo no let's
deberíamos iniciarlo con el cameo no a
see with the cameo that's true dude no no no
ver con el cameo eso es verdad tío no no
some  Juan's twe what are these
no unos twe de Juan a qué vienen estos
tweets about or can't the subject be touched I don't
tweets o no se puede tocar el tema no lo
know it's that I just read like a
sé es que acabo de leer como un un hilo
tweet thread of yours it goes by a I think eh it's that I do
de tweet suyo va por un creo eh es que
n't understand things and I read it
no me entero de las cosas y lo he leído
just now it's that I don't those rolls I think it's a it's that she got
justo ahora es que yo no esos rollos
angry with
creo que es un es una se ha enfadado con
a tiktoker with Jerry maybe or something like that
una tiktoker con Jerry puede ser o algo
[ __ ] This is me don't get out get out get out of
así [__] Este soy yo no sal sal sal
there Get out of there what are you
sal de ahí Sal de ahí qué estáis
saying dude what dude no no no no don't put
diciendo tío que tío no no no no metéis
the God dude what are you talking about I love it I love it
el Dios tío de qué estáis hablando Me
because you don't like to
encanta me encanta porque no os gusta
talk about somewhat thorny issues that that that I don't give a damn
nada hablar de temas un poco espinosos
or rather
que que que que me la pela o sea
let's talk who the [ __ ] Jerry is yes Jerry
hablemos quién [__] es Jerry si Jerry
I think it's you Jerry too Me too but I
Pienso que eres tú Jerry tamb Yo también
said that she was a tiktoker I
per lo he dicho que era una tiktoker No
'm neither a nor a tiktoker I mean it's not
soy ni una ni tiktoker O sea que no soy
me
yo
well
bueno
I'm not either well then that's it let's not talk that's it that's it's it's it's
Yo tampoco soy pues entonces ya está no
next no but let Juani come in and
siguiente no pero que entre Juani y lo
tell it No but what are we
cuente No pero qué somos
now save me from Oliveira Oliveira
ahora el sálvame del oliveira oliveira
I am if you are a man woman  or child or adult
soy si seas hombre mujer o niño o adulto
if I mess with you Answer me don't
si me meto contigo Respóndeme a mí no
involve me Well then let's do
involucres a mi Bueno pues vamos a hacer
the job that espurcito has entrusted to us
la labor que nos ha encomendado
Okay and let's do
espurcito Vale y vamos a hacer aquí
our sálvame delux here let's see what
nuestro sálvame delux a ver lo que ha
happened Juan Guarnizo says on Twitter there are
pasado Juan guarnizo dice en Twitter hay
good days and days when Movistar
días buenos y días en los que Movistar
esport uploads a minute-long clip of you
esport sube un clip tuyo de un minutillo
to their
a su
account and ends up with 3000 people
cuenta y termina con 3000
cited okay let's see but We'd have to see
citados vale a ver pero Habría que ver
first We'd have to see which one is
primero Habría que ver cuál es el cuál
the
es el tet de
Movistar tet that has had those cited
Movistar que ha tenido esos citado
wait and see let's go
espérate a ver vamos a
look for it My heart is broken how are
buscarlo Tengo roto el corazón cómo van
those going Live family for you I'm a mistake let's
esos Live familia para ti soy un error a
see a clip of
ver un clip de
Juan a clip from
Juan un clip de
today we talk about the rigu hispano too eh
hoy se habla del rigu hispano también eh
then we'll comment let's see
luego comentamos a
I thought it was Mayichi I don't know who it
ver me creía que era mayichi no sé quién
is
es
eh a clip of Juan on Movistar esport
eh un clip de Juan en Movistar esport
But this is already
Pero esto ya es el 5 de
October 5th Good night Javi I hope you
octubre Buenas noches Javi Espero que
are well I send you a big hug
estés bien Te mando un fuerte abrazo
greetings I'm so-so I'm so-so
saludos estoy regulín estoy regulín hijo
my son I'm so-so  the truth is
mío estoy regulín la verdad es
that I feel very
que me encuentro muy
dull the worst thing is that now I'm not going to
apagado lo peor es que ahora no voy a
be sleepy because I woke up
tener sueño porque que me he despertado
at 7 or 8 in the evening today I say I'm going to
a las 7 8 de la tarde hoy digo voy a
sleep hard to see if I
dormir a tope a ver si ya me
wake up
despierto
powerful but no no let's see I don't see
potente pero no no a ver yo no veo
any cli here from Juan War nison
ningún cli aquí de de Juan War nison
mstar Sport
mstar Sport
today I mean they've deleted it for sure
hoy o sea lo han borrado seguro
no for sure since Juan has complained
no seguro que como Juan se ha quejado
for sure they've deleted it because these
seguro que la han borrado porque esta
people are really lukewarm eh Sisi
gente son unos tibios de cuidado eh Sisi
for the Crusade of the
para la Cruzada de la
gentlemen for our for our
señoreros para nuestra para nuestra
Crusade
Cruzada
eh the kids here no they're not going to
eh los chavales de aquí no no van a
understand what we're talking about
entender de lo que estamos hablando
we're talking about a lady who gets
estamos hablando una señora que le saca
money from another lady it's a very
la pasta a otra es una historia muy
long story okay And then she makes her think
larga vale Y entonces le hace pensar
that to get the money she makes her think
que para sacarle la pasta le hace pensar
that I insult her that I have a
que yo la insulto que yo tengo una
war with her and that the way to
guerra con ella y que la forma de
answer me is by giving her money I mean like it's
contestarme Es dándole pasta a ella o
very long okay it's
sea en plan es que es muy largo vale es
very long Don't tell me what's going on Okay very
muy largo No me digas que va Bueno muy
well I'm glad that Irene is
bien yo me alegro de que Irene nos
helping us in this in this Crusade that we
ayudes en esta en esta Cruzada que
have because this is a Crusade
tenemos porque esto es una Cruzada
because this is a  Crusade by herself eh I
porque esto es una Cruzada ella sola eh
mean how disgusting man how disgusting
O sea qué asco tío qué
how
repugnancia qué
disgusting that she helps us, helps us in this
asco que nos ayude que nos ayude en esta
Crusade that we have because this is a
Cruzada que tenemos porque esto es una
Crusade and and no, she doesn't have any Crusade, I
Cruzada y y no no tiene ninguna Cruzada
mean, I've already asked her for 40 months
o sea yo ya hace ya 40 meses que le pedí
not to mention me anymore and the the the girl
que no me mencionara más y la la la tía
all [ __ ] day about me all day how
todo el [__] día de mí todo el día qué
disgusting a 70 year old lady all day
asco una señora de 70 años todo el día
talking about my member about I don't know what and
hablando de mi miembro de no sé qué y
all to get money out of the other guy I
todo para sacarle dinero a la otra tío o
mean today she got it right, I've
sea hoy le ha
already
sacado bueno eso ya eso ya lo he
mentioned that before, gossip but my goodness what she got
comentado anteres salseo pero madre mía
out of it eh And she says very well
lo que la ha sacado eh Y dice muy bien
Thank you for helping us in this Crusade
Gracias por ayudarnos en esta Cruzada
as if giving her money was some
como si darle dinero a ella fuera algún
kind of
tipo de
argument give the boys Who is
argumento ponle a los chicos Quién es
Irene no No, we're not going to here Well,
Irene no No aquí no vamos a Bueno aquí
we're not going to talk about that here let's see what
no vamos a hablar de eso a ver ya lo que
I'm left with is this, we have to stop it, I
me queda es esto hay que frenarlo ya lo
've already said it on telesalseo if it's not stopped
he dicho en telesalseo si no se frena
by good means it will be stopped another way
por las buenas se va a frenar otra forma
but it's very repulsive
pero es muy repulsivo
eh man who is 70 years old here's the girl  there
eh tío que tiene 70 años está la tía ahí
and come My member come Javi to have
y venga Mi miembro venga Javi para tener
600 700 viewers so that the other
600 700 espectadores para que la otra le
is giving him money eh how shady the lords
esté dando dinero eh qué turbio el lores
of the lords
de la señoreros
shady How strange man it tastes like
turbio Qué raro tío me sabe a
beer it tastes like beer man I
cerveza me sabe a cerveza tío tengo
even have the taste today strange
hasta el gusto hoy raro
man the cross that I end you with her
tío la cruz que te acao a ti con ella
Well we'll see until
Bueno ya lo veremos hasta
when but well it's going to get more muddy
cuándo pero bueno más se va enturbiar
Exactly tesa when we get what we have to get
Exacto tesa cuando saquemos lo que
out it's that I don't know how I
tenemos que sacar es que yo no sé cómo
well I would tell you I don't know how she
se Yo bueno yo te diría no sé cómo se
dares she dares Because she doesn't care she
atreve se atreve Porque le da igual no
has no shame and she doesn't care about her
tiene vergüenza y le da igual su
dignity her family's her
dignidad la de su familia la de sus
children's she doesn't care what she wants
hijos le da igual ella lo que quiere que
the other one having money But well sisuka
la otra estando pasta Pero bueno sisuka
thanks for your money for the
gracias por por tu dinero para la
Crusade Thank you for your
Cruzada Gracias por tu
money whether you are a man woman child or adult
dinero seas hombre mujer niño o adulto
but what I would like is to see
pero es que lo que me gustaría es ver
what is What is the cli
qué es lo que está Cuál es el cli
uncle luar we don't know What is the clican
tío luar no sabemos Cuál es el clican
shared on Movistar Sport Well of course I'm
compartido en Movistar Sport Pues claro
missing a part of the context to
me falta ahí una parte del contexto para
know what a disgusting rep
saber qué asco repu
because she wants easy money from the chick no
porque quiere dinero fácil de la tipa no
no but money  I don't know in all the
no pero dinero yo ya no sé en todos los
months that it has been going on how much money she has taken from him
meses que lleva cuánto dinero le habrá
if she already warned that she was going to
sacado si ella ya avisó que le iba a
take the money from him, she already warned him but I don't know, I don't know how far she is
sacar la pasta ella ya lo avisó pero ya
going to take it from him, I don't know how far they are going to
no sé no sé hasta dónde le va a sacar no
fleece her but it is shady
desplumar pero es turbio
eh they are doing Santos well anyway
eh están haciendo Santos bueno en fin
come on whether you are a man, woman, child or adult
venga ya seas hombre mujer niño o adulto
if I mess with you Answer me don't
si me meto contigo Respóndeme a mí no
involve my family because that
involucres a mi familia porque eso
shows that you have no arguments and
demuestra que no tienes argumentos y
you are garbage without
eres basura sin
more nobody ever goes against me from the
más nadie nunca va contra mí desde el
stupidest youtuber to the kid with
youtuber más estúpido hasta el niño con
the profile picture of the smooth Cat
la foto de perfil del smoth Cat
involving my family when many
involucrar a mi familia cuando muchas
times they have absolutely nothing to
veces no tienen absolutamente nada que
do with it only clarifies to me that I am right and I
ver Solo me aclara que tengo la razón y
will continue to be right the vast majority
la voy a seguir teniendo la gran mayoría
of the time on the internet today If
de las veces en el internet actual Si
you speak it is wrong if you remain silent it is wrong I'm tired if you
hablas está mal si callas está mal Ya me
have to say something It is ridiculous it is
si hay que decir que algo Es ridículo se
said and that's it obviously keeping the
dice y listo obviamente conservando los
manners nobody has to share your point of
modos nadie tiene que compartir tu punto
view because it is Simply that a
de vista porque es Sencillamente eso un
dog's point of
perro punto de
view In conclusion I am like a [ __ ]
vista En conclusión estoy como una [__]
rock I am like a [ __ ] rock this year
roca estoy como una [__] roca este año
I fell to the  deeper on an emotional level
caí a lo más hondo a nivel anímico
because I let failures sink me
porque dejé que fracasados me hundiera
but stop
pero ya no más
crying and sucking for these three twe I'm going
lloren y mamen por estos tres twe Yo iré
to an amusement park and I'll light it up I'll
a un parque de diversiones y prenderé
see you there in a while
irl allí nos vemos al ratito
friends let's see there's a lot of reading here
amigos a ver hay muchas lecturas aquí
eh On one hand it catches my attention what you
eh Por un lado me llama la atención lo
mean by
hundieron A qué se refiere con
failures
fracasados me
sink me to Dallas do you think it's a thorn in the
hundiera al Dallas creéis que es una pua
Dallas you're putting in the
al Dallas estáis poniendo en el
chat I'm not I haven't seen that anyone
chat Yo es que no no he visto que nadie
has sunk her let's see she's been criticized for
la haya hundido a ver se le ha criticado
an attitude she's been criticized for several
una actitud se le ha criticado varias
attitudes But as
actitudes Pero como se le critican a
everyone is criticized but it hasn't been like a crushing
todos pero no ha sido como un machaque
against Juan or everyone against
contra Juan ni todos contra
Juan There are things in which people do
Juan Hay cosas en las que la gente pues
n't agree with him period
no está de acuerdo con él punto
but then in the end cry and suck
pero ya luego el final lloren y mamen
for these three tweets I'm going to an amusement park
por estos tres tweet Yo iré a un parque
Like my bed is better
Así un poco como lo de mi cama es mejor
than yours
que la tuya
eh it's normal that you have nothing to say
eh normal que no tengan nada que decir
since I was 22 I spent my
desde los 22 años me pasé la
life your ego is As High As You
vida tu ego es Tan Alto Como tu
hypocrisy No my ego is much
hipocresía No mi ego es muchísimo más
higher how badly Juan manages this man I
alto qué mal gestiona Juan esto tío o
mean this is terrible
sea esto está fatal
eh come on this sounds like a [ __ ] mess
eh sea es que Esto suena a ninda rechi
since I was 22 I spent my life let's see
desde los 22 años me pasé la vida a ver
man what the [ __ ] are you going to spend your life at
tío qué [__] te vas a pasar la vida con
22 years old still at 22 years old you still don't
22 años todavía con 22 años todavía no
know what life is
sabes lo que es la vida
Juan what are you going to spend what
Juan qué te vas a pasar lo que es la
life is if you still don't know what
vida si todavía no sabes lo que es la
life is the only thing you've been lucky enough to
vida lo único que has tenido la suerte
have money
de tener dinero
man I mean but I didn't expect this from
tío o sea pero yo no me esperaba esto de
Juan
Juan
[Music]
[Música]
eh I didn't expect Juan to be like this
eh yo no me esperaba que Juan sería así
eh I mean I spent my life What a life you've
eh o sea me pasé la vida Qué vida te has
spent You know what it's like to spend your
pasado Tú sabes lo que es pasarse la
life Juan spending your life is that you can
vida Juan pasarte la vida es que puedas
go on for 3 years with a salary
tirar para adante 3 años con un sueldo
of 800 raising your daughter
de 800 sacando a tu hija adelante
helping out at your mother's house paying
ayudando en casa de tu madre pagandole
rent and not owing any bills
alquiler y no debiendo ninguna factura
that's spending your life You went on the
eso es pasarte la vida Tú te pusiste en
internet to make minutes for the Dead and
internet a hacerle min aturas al Dead y
you got close to Ari Gameplay and you
te arrimaste al Ari Gameplay y te
became a millionaire What a life you've
hiciste millonario Qué vida te has
spent you've had  very
pasado tú lo has tenido
easy you haven't spent your
facilísimo tú no te la has pasado la
life you've drunk it because you've
vida tú te la has bebido porque a ti te
had luck But there are people who don't
ha tocado suerte Pero hay gente que no
have luck When you have
tiene suerte Cuando tengas
uh more maturity and when you go through more
eh más madurez y cuando pases por más
experience then you will know eh that there
experiencia pues entonces sabrás eh que
are things that money can't
hay cosas que el dinero no pueden
solve So when you know how to
solucionar Entonces cuando sepas
face situations in which
afrontar situaciones en las que el
money won't be able to get you out
dinero no te va a poder sacar pues
then You will know how to spend your life or you don't
entonces Te sabrás pasar la vida o tú no
spend your life Juan Because the
te pasas la vida Juan Porque tú en el
moment you have to face
momento que te tienes que enfrentar a
criticism you start crying in a
críticas te pones a llorar en una
corner and to get out of that you say Ah
esquina y para salir de eso te pones Ah
I'm going to an amusement park
me voy a un parque de atracciones
chincha raviña that's not spending your
chincha raviña eso no es pasarse la
life he
vida
has no idea what life is he's
no tiene ni idea de lo que es la vida es
a
un
kid he's a kid but on
chaval es un chiquillo pero es que
top of that he's had a very easy life he's
encima ha tenido la vida muy fácil ha
been lucky on the
tenido suerte en
internet creating content and and and
internet creando contenido y y y
hanging out with the D with Ar and with I don't know
juntándose con el D con Ar y con no sé
who he's blown it up okay he's blown it up very
quién lo ha petado vale lo ha petado muy
well but he's become a millionaire the
bien pero se ha hecho millonario que
fact that you succeed on the internet and
hecho de que t triunfes en internet y te
become a millionaire is not spending your life it's
hagas millonario no es pasarte la vida
that you've been lucky and
es que has tenido suerte y te han ido
the  things are good here but that's not all
las cosas bien aquí pero eso no es toda
life, I mean so old fashioned You won't
la vida o sea tan pasado de la vida No
be there when with two criticisms you
estarás cuando con dos críticas te
lock yourself in a corner of your room
encierras en una esquina de tu cuarto
Juan but this is also this is
Juan pero es que esto además esto es
embarrassing I mean this When I see him
vergonzoso o sea esto Cuando lo vea a él
in two or three years without going any further
dentro de dos o TR años sin ir más lejos
eh three or four years when he reads this he'll be
eh tres o cu años cuando lea este t le
ashamed
da vergüenza
and I'm going to shut up and I'm going to
y me voy a callar y me voy a
shut up I spent my life I'm going to shut up
callar me pasé la vida me vo a callado
Juan I had shut up Juan you
Juan me hab a callado Juan mejo
spent your
te pasaste la
life You went too far it's that I'm going to shut up
vida Te pasaste es que me voy a callado
because I don't want to get into other
porque ya no quiero entrar en otras
things but no you haven't spent your
cosas sabes pero no no te has pasado la
life at all listen to me when you've
vida para nada hazme caso que cuando has
had to face life you haven't faced it listen to me
tenido que enfrentar la vida no la has
Juan stupid people when they argue and
Juan la gente pendeja cuando discute y
have no arguments they bring up things that have
no tiene argumentos saca mete cosas que
nothing to do with it Just because they know
no tiene nada que ver Solo porque saben
that it
que te
bothers you the late they are stupid Juan their
molesta el late son [__] Juan su
personality is based on throwing [ __ ] at you
personalidad se basa en tirarte [__]
the cring peak on the
el pico del cring en
internet when I talked about money you are a
internet cuándo hablé de dinero eres un
complex well Juan you talk about money
acomplejado pues Juan hablas de dinero
at the moment you are saying that at
en el momento que estás diciendo que con
22 you went too far  life I mean now he's
22 te pasaste la vida o sea ahora está
saying that I never talk about money
diciendo que nunca hablo de dinero
So what do you mean at 22 you
Entonces a qué te refieres que con 22 te
spent your life what do you
pasaste la vida en qué te
mean
refieres
but I'm missing the click
pero es que me falta el clic
luare I'm missing the click I don't know what Juan is
luare me falta el click no sé a qué está
responding to
respondiendo
totally totally it's
Juan total total es
true it's true it's true it's true
verdad es verdad es verdad es verdad
what it says there place in the script is
esto que pone ahí lugar en el guion es
true yesterday Juan was
verdad ayer Juan estaba
asking yesterday Juan was
pidiendo ayer Juan estaba
asking and in fact he even put the
pidiendo y de hecho puso incluso la
full screen he put it's true because he
pantalla completa puso es verdad porque
wanted them to take a clip for
quería que le sacaran clip para
tiktok it's true it's true
tiktok es verdad es verdad
that yesterday Juan was asking to go on
que ayer Juan estaba pidiendo salir en
tiktok let's see let's see I'm going to put myself here
tiktok a ver a ver Me voy a poner aquí
because I want to do well for tiktok and
que quiero salir bien para tiktok y
now they've co cl they've put it on Twitter and he
ahora han co cl han puesto en Twitter y
's
está
whining
lloriqueando
Oh I feel so bad and the place
Ay me encuentro regulín y el lugares me
is sending me gossip
está mandando salseo
guy he's crying
tío está llorando
because he wanted them to upload it to tikt not
porque quería que lo subieran a tikt no
Twitter but I mean the guy takes it
a Twitter pero o sea es que el tío coge
's true dude What a good memory he has
es verdad tío Qué buena memoria tiene
luare gachon Let's see luare says he
luare gachon A ver dice luare que me
's sending me something else but I'm going
está mandando algo más pero yo me voy
no to see I'm going to see how many members
no a ver voy a ver cuántos miembros
you have given today and if I don't I'm
habéis dado hoy y si no me
going I have a
voy
broken five members  tonight all
Tengo roto el cinco miembros hoy en toda
night with five members what
la noche con cinco miembros que
do we do with five members what do we
hacemos con cinco miembros que
do with five members we do
hacemos con cinco miembros no hacemos
nothing Look sisuka given away 10 H my
nada Mira sisuka regalado 10 H mi
sisuka but is she going to give them all away
sisuka pero los va a regalar todos
sisuka or
sisuka o
what is
qué
the news sending
la actualidad manda
ea No man let's see luar He's sending me
ea No hombre a ver luar Me está mandando
another topic and here we have
otro tema y aquí tenemos
another if you've been here less than an hour it's
otro si llevas menos de una hora es
true We've been here for an hour and a half It's
verdad Llevamos una hora y media Es
true It's true We've been here for an hour and a
verdad Es verdad Llevamos una hora y
half nothing more I believe that we've been here a
media nada más me crea yo que llevamos
long time your body
muchoo tu cuerpo
is good today there's news about the
es bueno hoy hay novedades sobre el tema
rwi issue I don't know if you were watching these past few days let's see I don't know if you've been
del rwi no sé si estuvisteis
watching the news these past few days
no sé si habéis estado viendo estos días
[Music]
[Música]
but do you remember
pero os acordáis que el año
last year let's see we could Search
pasado a ver podríamos Buscar el año
last year Beatriz how is this
pasado Beatriz qué tal este hombre
mature and rock man finally will defend his
maduro y de roca por fin defenderá a sus
friends and tell gre what he really
amigos y le dirá a gre lo que realmente
thinks of him Instead of playing and
piensa de él En lugar de jugar y
pretending
fingir
no No
no No
man Thank you very much for your 10
hombre Muchas gracias por tus 10
members Thank you very much let's see I want to
miembros Muchísimas gracias a ver quiero
see the end of the rewind from
ver el final del rewind del año
last year How it
pasado Cómo
ended because it sounds to me like he said he wouldn't do it anymore
terminó porque es que me suena que dijo
more no Or I'm
que ya no haría más no O me lo estoy
making it up
inventando
possible so you know if they've come
posible así que ya sabéis si se han
together I'm making it up maybe
juntado me lo estoy inventando a lo
not and before finishing I'd like to thank
no y antes de finalizar agradecer a
all the creators who have come together
todos los creadores que se han juntado
to finance this video and make it
para financiar este vídeo y hacerlo
possible so you know if you want to rew
posible así que ya sabéis si queréis rew
next year 50 million Likes Just
el año que viene 50 millones de Likes Es
kidding let's go for those 5 million
broma vamos a por esos 5 millones de
likes share it give it support and I hope you
likes compartirlo dadle apoyo y espero
loved it No man Yes yes he said he would do it
encantado No hombre Sí si dijo que haría
yes he said he would do it
si dijo que
every year the last one no it's not that yes
haría todos los años el último no es que
yes it seems to me that when he said there wasn't one it
sí sí me suena que cuando dijo que no
was from 21 to 22 but of course
había era del 21 para el 22 pero claro
how could there not be one this gives
cómo no va a haber esto le da un
him a fortune what happens is that he doesn't
pastizal a él lo que pasa que él no lo
he always plays and he lies to you and tells you
él siempre juega y y te miente y te dice
no that it costs him money that I do
que no que que le cuesta el dinero que
n't know what I've already been saying in
no sé qué ya lo he estado diciendo en
the previous videos every year
los vídeos anteriores todos los años
we repeat the same thing okay every year
repetimos lo mismo vale todos los años
we repeat the same thing Alex cool eh Not
repetimos lo mismo Alex molón eh No
only does he make money if not he wouldn't do it it's
solamente gana pasta si no no lo haría
worth a lot of money with the rewine but it also
vale muchísima pasta con el rewine sino
gives a lot of promotion to his company I mean
que le da mucha promo a su empresa o sea
this has given him a lot  a lot of
esto le ha dado muchísima muchísima
proma to your
proma a su
company and this is the last thing
empresa y esto ya lo último lo de de
this year Of course, of course, of course Yes, yes,
este año Claro claro claro Sí sí
we're
sí hemos
back, you
vuelto
will have full creative control to
tendrá todo el control creativo para
introduce the necessary joke Second,
introducir la broma necesaria segundo
no creator will be forced to do a
ningún creador será forzado a hacer una
scene, no, this is justifying, let's see what you
escena no esto es justificando a ver lo
're doing here,
que está haciendo aquí
eh Let's see, this is something that would have to be
eh A ver ellos esto es que habría que
compiled, luar,
recopilar luar
a change is missing there, no, no, but listen to me,
falta un cambio ahí no no pero escúchame
this is something that would have to be compiled well,
esto es que habría que recopilar bien
the times that they have said that the
las veces que han dicho que el
rin Look at the ruan at first they did it
rin Mira el ruan al principio lo hacían
with almost zero budget, okay, then they
con casi cero presupuesto vale luego lo
did it with what they did, I remember it was with a, well, I do
hacían con lo hicieron me acuerdo que
n't remember if it was 10,000
una pues no me acuerdo si fueron 10,000
or something like that, no, then they did it with
o algo así no luego lo hicieron con
15, I remember they did like an
15 me acuerdo que hicieron como un
event on twitter to raise funds And they
evento en twit para recaudar fondo Y con
did it with those funds, okay, then it
esos fondos lo hicieron vale luego
turns out that last year they needed or
resulta que el año pasado necesitaban o
the other
el otro
150,000, that they needed 150,000
150.000 que que que necesitaban 150.000
euros to make that
eur para hacer ese
video, Okay, and then I don't know, but every year
vídeo Vale y y luego no sé pero cada año
that passes, every year that passes, it seems that
que pasa cada año que pasa parece que
the rewind is costing them a lot, I don't know,
les cuesta mal el rewind yo que sé sube
the price of the materials goes up  I mean, look,
el precio de los materiales o sea fíjate
no I mean, an event that, in addition to
tú no O sea un evento que además de que
giving you an incredible amount of money because that
te da una pasta increíble porque ese
video generates a lot of money on
vídeo genera un dineral en
YouTube, that video generates a lot of money on
YouTube ese vídeo genera un dineral en
YouTube with those views promoting itself
YouTube con esas visitas promocionándose
almost a year and not only that but the
cas al año y ya no solamente eso sino la
promotion that has been given to your company with that and
promo que ha dado a su empresa con eso y
all the idiots of all the youtubers
todos los tontos de todos los youtubers
collaborating for free
colaborando gratis
there, this does not unite the community It is
ahí no es que esto une la comunidad Es
that this does not unite any community,
que esto que no une ninguna comunidad
man, what unites the community is that they are from the little
tío que une la comunidad que son del
group of these people, period. It does not
grupito de esta gente punto No
represent the community, this outright
representa la comunidad esto alto
saying it generates more than 100,000
decirlo genera más de 100000
man, more than 100,000 euros, let's see, I'm telling you, let's see, I'm
hombre más de 100000 eur a ver te
telling you, last year for
digo a ver te digo el del año pasado por
example, let's see, 2021.
ejemplo vamos a ver del 2021
Look,
Mira
you have a video with 22 million views,
tienes un vídeo de 22 millones de visita
a video with 22 million views of 20
un vídeo de 22 millones de visit de 20
minutes,
minutos
this is one of these videos, it's 40, 50,000
esto es un vídeo de estos son 40 50.000
bucks,
pavos
easily unless you haven't
tranquilamente a no ser que no le haya
put the ads in well and that, but
metido bien los anuncios y eso pero
come on, very little, put 20 or
vamos como muy poco ponle 20 o
30,000 is worth
30.000 vale
more than the peaks you have here from the
más los picos que tienes por aquí de los
making no and the outtakes I don't know
making no y las tomas falsas no sé s
what the 30 40,000 bucks there's no one to
cuá los 30 40000 pavos no hay quien te
take it away from you but it's This video if I
lo quite pero es Es que este vídeo si
remember correctly Had a money collection on
recuerdo Tuvo una recolecta de dinero en
Twitch then
Twitch luego el del año
last year's no No
pasado no No
lie it's that I don't remember by
mentira es que ya no me acuerdo de
heart I would have to review it but there was
memoria tendría que revisarlo pero hubo
one that was a Twitch collection there was
uno que fue una recolecta de Twitch hubo
another there was another
otro hubo otro
that the guy took because they've done some
que el tío cogió porque han hecho unas
dirty things behind this video there have always been
guarrerías detrás de este vídeo siempre
other peaks behind okay I mean there was
habido otra pichos detrás vale o sea
another one there was a year I don't know if it was the
otro hubo un año no sé si fue el año
previous year or the other there was a year that he took it
anterior o el otro hubo un año que cogió
and said this year I already said last year he says I said it
y dijo este año ya dije el año pasado
would be the last rewind
dice dije que sería el último rewind
but it turns out that an anonymous producer appeared
pero es que aparecido un productor
who is going to put up all the money
anónimo que va a poner todo el dinero
without asking for anything in
sin pedir nada a
return well Well it turns out that I
cambio bueno Pues resulta ser que me
find out and I said it in
entero y lo dije en
that nobody echoed my exclusive
que nadie se hizo eco de mi exclusiva
but I said it exclusively then then it
pero lo dije yo en exclusiva luego luego
exploded okay but it turns out that that
estalló vale pero resulta ser que ese
producer who put up the
productor que puso la
pacha that producer who put up the pacha in
pacha ese productor que puso la pacha a
exchange for nothing was
cambio de nada era
gref and  What was the in exchange for nothing to
gref y Cuál era el a cambio de nada
broadcast it to break the record on his
emitirlo para romper el récord en su
Twitch channel and you say Well but it's normal
Twitch y tú dices Bueno pero es normal
no If he puts up the money and pays for the rewind
no Si él pone la pasta y paga el rewind
and wants to release it on his channel it's okay
y lo quiere estrenar en su canal está
no It's logical he hasn't spent
bien no Es lógico no se ha gastado
100,000 bucks 150,000 bucks whatever price they
100,000 pavos 150,000 pavos el precio
put on it Of course but you
que le pongan Claro pero es que tú
imagine a Willy Rex I don't know who I don't know
imagínate un Willy Rex no sé quién no sé
how much collaborating for free for
cuánto colaborando gratis para el canal
gref's channel, I mean always some filth and
gref o sea siempre unas guarrerías y
always some dealings and of course what
siempre unos trapicheo y claro lo que
everyone said was but
todo el mundo decía era pero
well you put in sponsorships and now the
bueno pones pones patrocinios y ya el
money no how much would it cost Just that all
dinero no cuánto costaría Solo que todos
the streamers reacted and promoted
los streamers reaccionaran y promocionar
a video of yours and all the smart ones
a un video tuyo y todos los listos
killing themselves to participate for free no no and
matándose por participar gratis no no y
all parties to participate
todos partidos se la cara por participar
eh how much would it cost man well I do
eh que cuánto costaría hombre pues yo yo
n't know how much can how much can
no sé cuánto te puede cuánto te puede
auron Play charge you
cobrar auron Play
eh how much can auron Play charge you or
eh cuánto te puede cobrar auron Play o
jordy Wild or I to dedicate a video to you on
jordy Wild o I por dedicarte un vídeo en
their channel I mean they all make a
su canal O sea que todos ellos hacen una
reaction of  rwi and uploads it to his
reacción del rwi y la sube a su
channel I mean it's a promo for it and they
canal O sea es una promo de la y
collaborate and collaborate on the video I mean they
colaboran y colaboran en el vídeo o sea
lose a day of work and they collaborate
pierden un día de su trabajo y colaboran
and act and travel I mean I've
y actúan y se desplazan o sea yo es que
never understood that the
eso nunca lo he entendido la
truth is I've never understood that And
verdad yo eso nunca lo he entendido Y
after the filth Alex cool
que después de la guarrerías Alex molón
with gref the two of them
con gref los dos
shutting him up that I went out to recognize him but I do
callándole que salí a reconocerlo pero
n't know what but I don't know how much you
no sé qué pero no sé cuánto
know that they continue collaborating on this
sabes que sigan colaborando en esto
Okay but the last straw is this the last
Bueno pero es que ya el colmo es esto el
straw is this because they said that there
colmo es esto porque ellos dijeron que
couldn't be brands there couldn't
es que no podía haber marcas no podía
be financing with brands because the
haber financiación con marcas porque las
brands set conditions I don't know what I don't
marcas ponían condiciones no sé qué no
know how much no that there couldn't be promos and it
sé cuánto no que no podía haber promos y
turns out that
resulta que el año
last year there was a promo
pasado sí que hubo ya promo
Mau
Mau
okay But well they keep quiet they keep
vale Pero bueno se lo callan se lo
quiet about it among themselves they keep things
callan entre ellos las cosas se las
quiet if someone else came along Maybe
callan si lo llegase otro A lo mejor
the bomb will explode okay but now the dick
estalla la bomba vale pero ya la [__]
is now the dick the dick the dick is that
es ya la [__] la [__] la [__] es
this year they have promos this year they
que que este año tiene promos este año
have sponsorships and this video this
tiene patrocinios y este vídeo este
trailer that you're watching is to
tráiler que estáis viendo es para
justify
justificar
now that the foot dies by the mouth the
ahora que por la boca muere el pie el
p difficult to get it out  you know
p difícil sacarlo sabes sea ya me dirás
you tell me why every year it's more difficult to get it
tú Por qué cada año es más difícil
out
sacarlo
why because because you go with filth
qué porque porque vas con guarrerías por
behind that's why because you go with
detrás al por eso porque vas con
filth behind And you go with
guarrerías por detrás Y vas con cosas
strange things behind but what happens every year
raras por detrás pero qué pasa cada año
it's more expensive is that they started
es más caro es que empezaron
doing it they started doing it with they
haciéndolo empezaron haciéndolo
started doing it with with 10,000
con empezaron haciéndolo con con 10.000
the rewine the first one Cost them 10 10,000
el rewine el primero Les costó 10 10.000
no the first rewine is in the
no el primer rewine está en la
interview with tiparraco the first No
entrevista con tiparraco el primero No
you know the first one that was popular they made it
tú sabes el primero que fue popular lo
cost 7000 it's in the
hicieron costó 7000 está en la
interview with tiparraco
entrevista de tiparraco
Look Javi I happen in audiovisuals and
Mira Javi yo ocurro en audiovisuales y
the costs of both filming and
los costes tanto de rodaje como de
post-production can skyrocket a lot
postproducción se pueden disparar mucho
I've made video clips with a 1k
yo he hecho videoclips con 1k de
budget and others with 30k you would be
presupuesto y otros con 30k te
surprised ps you are very sexy dad a
sorprendería pd estás muy sexy padre un
kiss yes yes no I'll tell you no but
beso que sí si no te digo que no pero
what I'm telling you is that the
que yo lo que te digo es
logical thing is that each time it
que que lo lógico es que cada vez te
costs you less money not more well let's see it
cueste menos dinero no más bueno a ver
depends of course on the locations and what
depende claro las localizaciones y lo
you want to invest obviously
que tú quieras invertir evidentemente
but if you the one from 3 years ago
pero que si tú el de hace 3 años te
cost 7000 Look at the 2019 Hispanic Ruan
costó 7000 Mira el ruan hispano 2019 le
cost 7000 okay look here it says it's 7000
costó 7000 vale mira aquí lo dice é 7000
the 2019 rewind okay
el rewind del 2019 vale
look and it's one of the most handsome there is, it's one
mira y es de los más guapos que
of the coolest there was
hay es de los más chulos que hubo
Look, very cool it will always be the best
Mira chulísimo siempre será el mejor
Battle
Battle
royale this one for me if it's not the best I
royale este para mí si no es el mejor yo
think this was the best it cost 7000
creo que este fue el mejor le costó 7000
Well then this one cost 7000 which
Bueno pues pues este le costó 7000 que
is more than recovered, let's not be
está más que recuperado no sea estamos
talking about the one from 2019 Well look I'm telling you I'm telling you
hablando el de 2019 Pues mira os digo os
Look
digo Mira
2019 what would this making off be Look it would
2019 cuál es sería este making off Mira
n't be This look 25 billion You know what they
no sería Este mira 25000 millones Tú
are Uy 25 billion You
sabes lo que son Uy 25000 millones Tú
know what 25 million views are
sabes lo que son 25 millones de visitas
a 15
un vídeo de 15
minute video, come on This is recovered by
minutos vamos Esto está recuperado por
three and by four and by five plus the
tres y por cuatro y por cinco más el
half hour making off of 4 million
making off de media hora de 4 millones
views, that is, only in the
de de visita o sea solamente en el
making off it is more than
making off ya está más que
recovered But how does this 7000 cost you
recuperado Pero cómo te cuesta este
How does this cost you  7000 the
7000 Cómo te cuesta este 7000 el del año
next year you do it with 10,000 because
siguiente te lo haces con 10.000 porque
they did like a collection on Twitch and
hicieron como una recolecta en Twitch y
now suddenly the other one needs front
ahora de repente el otro necesita fente
and the other one already needs 150,000
y el otro ya necesita 150.000
turkeys 150,000 turkeys of course and now you say
pavos 150.000 pavos claro y ahora dices
gref
gref
the special 10 million gref what
el especial 10 millones de gref que dijo
gref said How much did this cost him
gref Cuánto le costó
[Music]
[Música]
Alpha my life calmly you're thinking
Alfa mi vida con calma estás pensando
miso This
miso Este
video the 10 million
vídeo el especial de los 10 millones de
gref special cost him
gref le costó
40,000 it cost him 40,000 this one
40.000 le costó 40.000 este a
gref seems to have a weapon Okay
gref parece que tiene un arma Bueno
let's get closer it's like a
vamos a acercarnos que es como una
fortnite simulation It's weird it's weird
simulación del fortnite Es raro es raro
but it's what I'm telling you I mean it's not that it's
pero es lo que os digo O sea ya no es
weird anymore in Yes it's that I don't
que sea raro en Sí ya es que yo no
participate in a place where they've
participo en un sitio donde me han
tried to deceive me or rather it's that they
intentado engañar o sea es que les
tried to sneak in everyone I mean yes if I hadn't
intentaron colar a todos O sea si si no
jumped it in an exclusive
lo llego a saltar yo en una exclusiva
if I hadn't extended it they would
si no lo llego a alargar se encuentran
all meet at the end of the year with the rewind
todos a final de año con el rewind
airing on gref's Twitch Channel that's
emitiéndose en el en el Canal de Twitch
why
eso
all creative control to introduce
todo el control creativo para introducir
the necessary joke second no
la broma necesaria segundo ningún
creator will be forced to do a scene they will
creador será forzado a hacer una escena
not do
no realizarán
any promotions
promociones ninguna
[Music]
[Música]
promotion number 65 the rewind is from its
promoción número 65 el rewind es de su
community if it is financed it is with the
comunidad si se financia es con el
objective of continuing with the
objetivo de seguir con la
tradition
tradición
6 first promo
6 primera promo
al I think you and I speak the same
al creo que tú y yo hablamos el mismo
language
idioma
[Music] I
[Música]
mean look at the teaser look at
o sea fíjate tú ya el teaser fíjate tú
the teaser of the the teaser
ya el teaser de la el teaser
[Music]
[Música]
of the mess with the memes I mean but
de al lío con los memes o sea pero
look at you
fíjate tú
eh the tser eh the tser of the rewind that
eh el tser eh el tser del rewind que
represents the community is
representa la comunidad es
takis all dude they
takis todos tío se
sell out I mean the
venden o sea el
taser the
taser el
taser Javi as an economist you are a very good
taser Javi como economista eres muy buen
clown Fabricio you want to upload you want to
payaso Fabricio quieres subir quieres
upload Fabricio says where did you see that over
subir Fabricio dice dónde viste que con
time something that where did you see that something
el tiempo algo que dónde viste que algo
over time costs less It's obvious
con el tiempo cueste más barato Se nota
that you have no idea Fabricio I'm going to
que no tienes ni idea Fabricio voy a
understand that you're just any fool
entender que eres cualquier tonto
follower of these people and that's it Okay I
seguidor de esta gente y ya está Vale o
mean there are a million things that with the
sea hay un millón de cosas que con el
time they cost less VHS tapes
tiempo cuestan más barato las cintas vhs
there you have one Vinyl records there you
ahí tienes una los discos de vinilo ahí
have another one Radio cassette players
tienes otra la los radiocassette las
Plasma televisions There are a lot of
televisiones plasma Hay un montón de
things that cost less over
cosas que cuestan más baratas con el
time clown you're a clown you're an
tiempo payaso que eres un payaso eres
[ __ ] but literally it's that
gilipolla pero literalmente es que
apart literally it's that apart I
aparte literalmente es que aparte yo no
'm not referring to something costing
me estoy refiriendo a que algo cueste
less because of time you fool you're a [ __ ] fool
más barato por el tiempo tonto que eres
I'm referring to that It's
tonto de la [__] Yo me estoy refiriendo
logical that it costs you less
a que Es lógico que te cueste menos
because the first time the first time I
porque tú la primera vez la primera vez
understand that you need to buy more things
entiendo que necesitas comprar más cosas
okay Imagine the first time you
vale Imagínate la primera vez pues
buy the cameras the lights
compras las cámaras los focos
eh cranes
eh grúas
a lot of things for the equipment the
un montón de cosas para el equipo la
second time you already have them you don't have to
segunda vez ya las tienes no tienes que
buy so much then Go smell
comprar tanto entonces Vete a a olerle
your idol's farts al gref put your
los peos a tu ídolo al gref ponle la
face in his ass Okay and And get my dick out
cara en el culo Vale y Y sácate mi [__]
of your mouth I just stuck it in you go
de la boca que te la acabo de meter
on Oh really Fabricio you're very
anda Ay de verdad Fabricio que eres muy
stupid you're very stupid Fabricio come
tonto que eres muy tonto Fabricio venga
to your
a tu
house reviews Drake Coat Drake
casa críticas Drake Coat Drake
Coat has gone warm but it's that it's
Coat se ha ido calentito pero es que es
stupid has gone warm but it's that it's
tonto se ha ido calentito pero es que es
fool Aside from that you can take it and you can
tonto Aparte tú puedes [__] y puedes
put it in the chat Javi This is not like that
poner en el chat Javi Esto no es así
because I am an economist p p pi but for
porque yo soy economista p p pi pero que
you to enter the chat saying you are a
tú entres en el chat diciendo eres un
clown I am an economist as an economist you are a
payaso soy unc como economista eres un
clown or rather as an economist I insult you
payaso o sea como economista te insulto
Fabricio You are a [ __ ] clown you are not an
Fabricio Eres un [__] payaso que no eres
economist No, you don't even know how to write
economista No que no sabes ni escribir
my son you are going to be your
hijo mío vas a ser tu
economist take Fabricio to the Corner
economista lleven a Fabricio al Rincón
of thinking well let's see Drake Coat because
del pensar bueno a ver Drake Coat pues
alen molón lied about the rwin and the
alen molón mintió sobre el rwin y los
sponsors I don't understand what it
patrocinadores no entiendo qué le
cost him to say Until now it has been like this
costaba decir Hasta ahora ha sido así
But I see a sponsor as necessary
Pero veo necesario un patrocinador
because if not the accounts don't work out in
porque si no no salen las cuentas en
income that the accounts do work out
ingreso que sí le salen las cuentas
Of course the accounts work out what happens
Claro que salen las cuentas lo que pasa
is that he wants
es que él quiere
more and when he doesn't put 28 because
más y cuando no pone 28 porque por la
the p dies by the mouth
boca muere el
this year he is going to put
p este año te va a meter
this in you Ah of course Drake co I remember Drake co it's
este Ah claro Drake co ya me acuerdo
that Drake co had it
Drake co es que Drake co la tuvo el año
last year he had it clear
pasado la tuvo claro
Drake had it had it
Drake la
with Alex molón because he
la tuvo con con Alex molón porque se
started to complain yes yes yes yes yes yes
puso encima a quejarse sí sí
it's true they had it a
sí sí sí sí es verdad la tuvieron un
little bit here on Twitter
poquito aquí en Twitter
Yes but for the only reason that Alex
Sí pero por el único motivo que Alex
molón doesn't  It doesn't put 28
molón no no le pone 28
sponsors that do a rewind of
patrocinadores que hagan un rewind de
sauce a kiss brendy but apart from that I'm
salseo un beso brendy pero aparte de eso
going to tell you more I'm going to tell you more
os voy os voy decir más os voy decir más
eh apart from takis I'm not going to tell you this
eh aparte de takis esto no os lo va a
Eh I'm not going to tell you this but
decir Eh Esto no os lo va a decir pero
apart from
aparte de
takis there are going to be more brands in the rewind
takis va a haber más marcas en el rewind
that will do a
que harán una
passive promo and you will say
pasiva y ustedes diréis
and I will tell you Well look for now
y yo te diré Pues mira de momento
write this down and save it for January in
apuntaros esto y guardarlo para enero en
December January you tell me okay But there are going to
Diciembre enero me lo decís vale Pero va
be several brands there are going to be several
a haber varias marcas va a haber varias
brands on t-
marcas en
shirts for
camisetas por
example yes Karime Sure you're
ejemplo sí Karime Claro ya estás
taking too long
tardando camiseta
football stadium t-shirt Maybe the
estadio de fútbol A lo mejor las
banners save this click in the
pancartas a guardaros este click en el
rewind not only is takis going to be
rewind no solamente va a estar takis
sponsoring takis it is going to be the
patrocinando takis va a ser el
official sponsor But there are going to be more brands that
oficial Pero va a haber más marcas que
are going to put money in and finance the
van a poner pasta y van a financiar el
rewind in a more
rewind de manera más
discreet way a bottle on the table some
discreta una botella en la mesa una
info remember
info acordaros de
that a kiss
eso un beso
arica remember
arica acordaros de
that I have the impression that the
eso tengo la impresión de que el
original spirit has been lost just like
espíritu original Se ha perdido al igual
Alex molón suddenly became called Alex
que Alex molón pasó a llamarse Alex
Hernández  it's
Hernández de
business But I've been
repente es negocio Pero lo llevo
saying it Look at the business but I
diciendo Mira el negocio pero que esto
already saw this a couple of years ago in
esto ya lo vi yo hace un par de años en
the dealings and the little things they had
los trapicheos y las cosillas que tenían
behind the scenes but I already saw this
por detrás pero esto ya lo vi
What's up here media Pro media pro is
yo Qué pinta aquí media Pro media pro es
the agency media pro is the one that
la agencia media pro es la que ha
got the deal between Alex and him and
conseguido el acuerdo entre Alex y el y
takis I feel that takis financing the
takis siento que takis financiando el
rewind is going to make a lot of
rewind va a ser que muchos streamers
big streamers back out because they're not
grandes se echen para atrás porque no
going to give away their image
van a regalar su imagen
Exactly
Exacto
Exactly can you imagine If a PSOE flag appears, damn man
Exacto se imaginan Que aparezca una
I wouldn't be surprised at all if the
[__] tío no me extrañaría nada que el
scoundrel was sponsored by the PSOE
ruin estuviera patrocinado por el psoe
eh I wouldn't be surprised at all if this was
eh No me extrañaría nada que esto lo
financed by the PSOE remember what I'm
financiara el psoe acordaros de lo que
telling you if they were already crying with the filth they
digo si ya lloraban con la cochinada que
did with de
hicieron con de
gref it's that I don't know the truth what
gref es que no sé la verdad qué es lo
can happen I do
que puede pasar
n't know what can happen the
no sé qué es lo que puede pasar la
truth but well let's see luare is
verdad pero bueno a ver luare me está
making me wait because he says that there is
haciendo esperar porque dice que hay
something very
aquí algo muy
powerful here from carche But what happened what
potente de carche Pero qué ha pasado que
can be powerful from carch
puede haber potente de carch
luares The hispano rewind is only the
luares El rewind hispano es solo el
rewind of the Gamer no  represents the
rewind de los Gamer no representa el
content that I see on YouTube So
contenido que yo veo en YouTube Así que
for M it's yes and neither are we
para M es sis y ni de los Gamer tampoco
going to see the Gamer rewind, let's see
vamos a ver es el rewind de gre a ver
that cool kid Alex, he's a follower of
ese chico Alex molón él es seguidor de
him, he's a fan of gref or whatever, that's a
él es fan de gref o se ese ese es un
rewind that for him represents the
rewind que para él representa a a la
community But he refers to what he
comunidad Pero él se refiere a lo que él
knows as
conoce como
community, he refers to what he
comunidad él se refiere a lo que él
community
comunidad
luare Tell me where I can't
luare Dime dó no lo
find it luare I can't find it
encuentro luare no lo encuentro
king okay let's
rey vale a
see, he's processing them, he
ver está procesándolos
had it and at the end, do you also remember at the
tuvo y al final también os acordáis al
end of the screen,
final de la pantalla
Javi too Look at what Agustín
también Javi Fíjate lo que dijo Agustín
51 said that there were some youtubers who didn't
51 de que había algunos youtubers que no
want to record some scenes,
querían grabar algunas escenas
no, yes, this guy is earning
no que sí que este tío está ganando
a lot of money with that, but if not, he wouldn't
muchísimo dinero con eso pero que si no
do it, but that's how it is, you're not
no lo hace pero es que eso es así tú no
doing something that's not giving you
estás haciendo una cosa que no te está
results That's how it is, you're not
resultados Eso es así tú no estás
results,
resultados
well,
bueno
well, they're never going to tell me about
Bueno a mí no me van a decir nunca de
participating,
participar
Javier,
Javier
well, let's
bueno
see if
a ver si
Javi comes out, it's going to be the kinly rewind, I
sale Javi va a ser el rewind de la kinly
can see it coming, well there you go  a you
ya me lo veo venir pues ahí Vais a
have a ton of brands all that
tenéis un montón de marcas todas las que
Piqué wants to
quiera Piqué
put in I'm going to talk about everything imagine being
meter voy a hablar de todo imagínate ser
a kid who betrayed his friends
un pibe que traicionó a sus amigos
because his girlfriend asked him typical
porque su novia se lo pidió típico
kid without balls Congratulations carche it's
chaval sin [__] Felicidades carche se
obvious that you're going to get rich get barely 200
nota que te va dar mar pilla apenas 200
vi and that's it champion Look sler you know what the
vi y así campeón Mira sler sabes qu es
good thing about everything is that when I get to the
lo bueno de todo que yo cuando llego a
end of the month I don't have to worry about
fin de mes no me tengo que preocupar de
whether I can get enough food
si me llega la comida a la boca
ask your mother the same thing you [ __ ]
pregúntale lo mismo a tu madre [__]
[ __ ] eh first of all that
subnormal eh lo primero de todo eso lo
secondly I talk about whatever the hell comes out of my
segundo yo hablo de lo que me sale de
balls And what I think it is
los [__] Y de lo que creo que es
wait And wait this has been strong
espérate Y espérate ha sido fuerte esto
eh I'm going to talk about everything imagine being
eh lo voy a hablar de todo imagínate ser
a kid who betrayed his friends
un pibe que traicionó a sus amigos
because his girlfriend asked him typical
porque su novia se lo pidió típico
kid without balls Congratulations imagine
chaval sin [__] Felicidades imagínate
being a kid who betrayed his friends
ser un pibe que traicionó a sus amigos
just because his girlfriend asked him typical
solo porque su novia se lo pidió típico
kid without balls it's obvious that you're going to get
chaval sin [__] se nota que te va dar
rich get barely 200 viv  it shows I don't know
mar pilla apenas 200 viv se nota no sé
what I don't know how much that I haven't
qué no sé cuánto eso ya no lo he
understood anymore barely 800 viewers champion
entendido apenas 800 viewers campeón
Look slayer you know what the good thing about
Mira slayer sabes qué es lo bueno de
all of this is that when I make ends meet I don't have to
todo que yo cuando llego a fin de mes no
worry about whether the
me tengo que preocupar de si me llega la
food reaches my mouth ask
comida a la boca pregúntale lo mismo a
your mother the same thing you [ __ ] [ __ ] eh what if it
tu madre [__] subnormal eh lo si ha la
hurt her that
dolido eso
eh it hurt her eh first of all
eh le ha dolido eh lo primero de todo
that second I talk about what
eso lo segundo yo hablo de lo que me
comes out of my balls And what I believe
sale de los [__] Y de lo que creo que
is right and honest At the end of the
es correcto y honesto Yo al final del
day I have a clear conscience with
día tengo la conciencia tranquila con
my actions with what I've done in my life
mis actos con lo que he hecho en mi vida
with what I do in my life and so on
con lo que hago en mi vida y demás
and third if there's something that I'm
e y tercero si hay algo en lo que estoy
uneasy about or something that I'm not
intranquilo o algo en lo que no estoy
happy with thank God I go to the psychologist
contento gracias a Dios voy al psicólogo
for a day now eh I tell him my
desde hace un día eh Le cuento mis
things he helps me manage them eh
movidas me ayuda a gestionarlas eh yo
if I were you I would go to the
que tú iría o al
psychologist Okay and he's going to tell you something
psicólogo Vale y va a decirte una cosa
that I usually say to my teammates in
que le suelo decir a mis compañeros en
Valorant I can't say it live
el valorant no puedo decirla en directo
because I'm thrown out on channel
porque me tir es en canal
and I'm not going to say it okay eh But oh well
e no lo voy a decir vale eh Pero bueno
in 2020 you hung out with the Tops not in
en 2020 te juntabas con los Tops no en
2020 in fact eh I started streaming my
2020 de hecho eh empecé a streamear mi
first stream had a peak of 6,000
primer streaming tuvo un pico de 6,000
people and an average of 3,000 people I did
personas y una media de 3,000 personas
n't hang out with anyone because in fact I
no me junté con nadie porque de hecho yo
never wanted to hang out with anyone and besides
nunca quise juntarme con nada y aparte
I was called a mole in the Spanish police
se me llamaba topo en la policía de
rp I mean no, the first Stream
rp O sea que no que el primer Stream
had 6,000 viewers why because it
tuvo 6000 espectadores por qué porque ya
was already known
era conocido
no What a shame
no Qué pena
eh he must be in pain it must hurt him
eh tiene que estar le tiene que doler
a lot to have lost that
mucho haber perdido eso
man I don't know the
tío Yo es que no sé los
numbers that he could have reached in
números que habrá podido llegar a tener
salary how it must have translated
en en sueldo como se habrá traducido
but I imagine that this kid must
pero yo me imagino que este niño habrá
have worked with brands that neither I nor
habrá trabajado con marcas que ni yo ni
I have ever worked with I've worked with
yo he trabajado nunca yo trabajado con
very few brands because of the type of
muy pocas marcas por el tipo de
content that I
contenido que
make but I mean he was already known in
hago pero o sea él ya era conocido en
pain rp no And then one day he decided to
pain rp no Y entonces un día decidió
do Stream and Then of course people with
hacer Stream y Enton claro la gente con
the expectation I don't imagine
la expectación no me imagino
no my goodness because it must be
no madre mía por le tiene que estar
giving him a shame that it lasted so
dando una pena que le haya durado tan
little man
poco tío
and 6000 viewers on Twitch I don't know
e 6000 espectadores en Twitch no sé
how long  he will have had that
cuánto tiempo habrá tenido eso
but it must be really crazy eh that
pero tiene que ser muy loco eh ese
money eh it must be a lot of money
dinero eh tiene que ser un dineral
eh it must
eh
be a lot of money eh Let's see, I
tiene que ser un dineral eh A ver yo
know people who
conozco a gente que
with an average of 500
con con una media de 500
viewers on Twitch get maybe
espectadores en Twitch se sacan a lo
a little luck of 1000 thousand and some
mejor un suer decito de 1000 mil y pico
euros And I started just okay I set up
euros Y yo empecé de solo vale me monté
my roles I looked for support from my
mis roles me me busqué apoyo de mis
roleplay colleagues like I was
compañeros de rolplay como era
tarco and a lot of gray-haired people and so on So
tarco y mucha gente canosa y demás
no, I 2020 because they invite me to
e Así que no yo 2020 porque me inviten a
play Ah Román you consider that a
jugar Ah Román tú consideras eso una
barb says Román Javi don't you realize
puya dice Román Javi no te das cuenta
that he's throwing a barb at Auron again I
que otra vez le tira una pua a auron yo
have a clear conscience Javi
tengo la conciencia tranquila Javi date
realize that well I hadn't seen it
cuenta de esa pues no lo había visto yo
as a barb, a
como una pua una
barb or rather, Auron keeps throwing a barb at him
pua o sea le sigue tirando una pua auron
amongas It's not that I got together I set
amongas No es que me junte yo he montado
this up I did it alone okay another thing
esto lo he hecho yo solo vale otra cosa
is that I was lucky That
es que haya tenido suerte de Que
obviously a large
obviamente pues ha venido un gran
audience of people came to see a server and
Público de personas a ver un servidor y
I was roleplaying on that server but
yo estaba roleando en ese servidor pero
what is my role  I put it together
lo que es mi rol me lo he montado yo
all by myself Okay and the people who came to see me
solito Vale y la gente que venía a verme
came to see me for my role, not for anything else,
me venía a ver por mi rol no por otra
I put my roleplay in Spain rp together
cosa yo mi roleplay en Spain rp me lo
all by myself okay V without
monté yo solo de acuerdo V sin ayuda de
anyone's help I put it together all by myself I just went and
nadie me lo monté yo solo yo cogí y le
said to my mom
dije a mi madre
eh tell me a song And from there I
eh dime una canción Y a partir de ahí ya
went but it seemed very appropriate to me yesterday
tiré pero me pareció muy acertado ayer
what happened with Sprint because they threw
lo de lo de Sprint porque le tiraron
[ __ ] at him for a clip
[__] por un clip
throwing acid humor and humor no no
tirando humor ácido y humor no no humor
acid sarcastic humor and people throw
ácido sarcástico y la gente le tira
[ __ ] at him for that for doing acid humor and
[__] por eso por hacer humor ácido y
for doing sarcastic humor you know what
por hacer humor sarcástico sabes qué es
happens I missed the spr thing because I
lo que pasa lo de spr me lo perdí porque
was bad the spr thing if I'm not mistaken it
estuve malo lo de spr si no me equivoco
was against auron no depr I missed it
era contra auron no lo depr me lo perdí
because I was bad Obviously
porque estuve malo Que obviamente la
people can't take responsibility you can't
gente no se puede hacer cargo tú no te
take responsibility for everyone and
puedes hacer cargo de todo el mundo ni
neither can you take responsibility I
tampoco te puedes hacer cargo yo esto lo
commented on this a long time ago people who
comenté hace mucho tiempo la gente que
have very large communities you can't
tiene unas comunidad muy grandes tú no
exactly take responsibility for
te puedes hacer cargo exactamente de
everything that happens not in your community but
todo lo que pasa no en tu comunidad sino
in the people who watch you But it can happen
en la gente que te ve Pero puede pasar
to a greater or lesser extent depending on the
en mayor o menor medida dependiendo del
speech that you give as a person, I
discurso que des tú como persona me
get something to say, let's see what they
llega algo de decir a ver que me lo
're sending me around
están mandando por
here, let's talk about the tryhards, the
aquí hablemos de los tryhards están los
tryhards are destroying the
tryhards destruyendo la industria de los
video game industry. Hi, I'm b b, a youtuber from,
videojuegos Hola soy b b youtuber de
are the trer destroying the
están los trer destruyendo la industria
video game industry? What this, dude, the
de los videojuegos qué esto boludo el
secondary channel Aon Play, dude. Come on,
canal secundario Aon Play boludo Dale
Aon, that's it, dude, the
Aon ya está boludo ya pasó lo de los
trer success thing is over, and now also
trer éxito y ahora también
how did such a person from the community with such a
cómo tal persona de la comunidad con tal
person from the community have such a
persona de la comunidad ha tenido tal
rif and rafe and this is a [ __ ]
rif y rafe y esto está hecho una [__]
mess. If I don't take charge and take charge of
[__] si yo no cojo y me hago cargo de
my own community, then I can't
mi propia comunidad Entonces no me puedo
take charge of anything, and tomorrow
hacer cargo de nada y el día de mañana
I can't be responsible for anything, and I can't
yo no puedo ser responsable de nada y ni
blame anyone for anything when I can
puedo echar nada en cara cuando yo pueda
take charge and have been with the psychologist for several months
[__] y lleve ya varios meses con el
and know how to put all the ideas and
psicólogo y sepa poner todas las ideas y
all the things that I have in my
todas las cosas cosas que tengo en la
head in order and can have a
cabeza en orden y pueda tener una
narrative capacity to put
capacidad narrativa como para ponerlo
everything absolutely and completely in order
todo absoluta y completamente en orden
to curse all the dead
para cagarme en todos los muertos de los
morons who don't stop harassing me
subnormales que no me paran de acosar
all year, I mean, I swear on my
todo el año o sea te lo juro por mis
dead  that I'm going to do it I'm very
muertos que lo voy a hacer lo tengo
clear but come on very clear that I'll tell you already
clarísimo pero vamos clarísimo eso ya os
well no no no there's no more to me to me he
lo digo yo bueno no no no hay más a mí
says Justin bombs Renfe and he
me a mí dice Justin bombardea renfe y la
bombs it now but you want to
bombardeo ya pero tú tienes ganas de
bomb Renfe I mean no I don't
bombardear la renfe O sea que no
know if idol already with someone that you
no sé si ídolo ya con a alguien que le
appreciate is enough No because if you
tienes aprecio basta No porque si tú
appreciate a
tienes aprecio a una
person and it's not idolatry or
persona y no es idolatra o admiración
absolute admiration when they tell you to do something you
absoluta cuando te dicen que hagas algo
think about it when it's idolatry or
piensas cuando es idolatra o admiración
absolute admiration you don't think about it imminent breakup
absoluta no lo piensas ruptura inminente
between Abi and
entre Abi y
Carz but no I mean everything it's that it's what
carz pero no s o sea todo es que es lo
we've talked about before it's that the
que hemos hablado antes es que el
live the live is much more
directo el directo es muchísimo más
difficult eh to broadcast a worked content or
difícil eh emitir un contenido currado o
a content a different
un contenido un contenido diferente
innovative content and with the irls it happens and it's
innovador y con los irls pasa y es que
what I've been saying my whole [ __ ]
es lo que llevo diciendo toda la [__]
life it's because of trends and it is what there is and that's it
vida es por modas y es lo que hay y ya
and it will go by trends my whole [ __ ]
está y va a ir por modas toda la [__]
life with everything and end It's that it's that
vida con todo y fin Es que es que ya
we have already talked about this subject you know how
hemos hablado de este tema sabes cómo es
fashionable the
de moda el like
easy like is the content of the streamers is
fácil el contenido de los streamers es
[ __ ] [ __ ]
una [__] [__]
I'm  positioned in such a way as
estoy posicionado de tal manera como
to be able to put a tweet saying that
para poder poner un tweet diciendo es
today's streamers
que los streamers de hoy en día serie de
Minecraft series eh biz rap reaction with that
Minecraft eh reacción de biz rap con eso
you get 50,000 likes that's what there is but it's a formula that works different people who change that formula are the people who innovate and that creates another new fashion that's what there is it's something that is going to exist okay F
va en lo que va a existir vale F
big streamers there Sprint for the face
streamers grandes hay Sprint por la cara
no but
no pero
no also we have to understand the reason for the
no también hay que entender el motivo de
funas guys also you don't have to be
las funas chicos también no hay que ser
no guys what happens is that on Twitch
no chicos lo que pasa es que e en Twitch
since 2000 since 2020 I have known for a
desde 2000 desde 2020 yo que sé desde
long time as Cris said in
hace mucho tiempo como ha dicho Cris en
the video itself we are all the same all the time
el propio vídeo somos todo todo el rato
and when you have
los mismos y cuando tú tienes
coexistence in coexistence
convivencia en la convivencia se genera
friction is generated and when that friction is not carried out in
el roce y cuando ese roce no se lleva de
an adult and mature way when above
una manera adulta y madura cuando sobre
all it is over the internet when
todo es por internet cuando todo el
everyone has their ego through the roof it is
mundo tiene el ego por las nubes es
much more difficult and to manage it
muchísimo más difícil y gestionarlo
eh Because what do you think It's not as easy
eh Porque qué creéis Que no es tan fácil
as just taking it and saying I'll open it
como [__] y decir yo lo abro por
privately with this  person and I talk to my
privado con esta persona y hablo con mi
community and I say this doesn't work like this,
comunidad y digo esto no funciona así
this shouldn't be done because I am
esto no hay que hacerlo porque yo soy
an adult and I can talk if
una persona adulta y puedo hablar si
I have a problem with x or with i what do you
tengo un problema con x o con i qué
think It's not easy No but I don't know it does
creéis Que no es fácil No pero eso no se
n't happen why Because there is
no pasa por qué Porque hay
ego, that's what there is, that's what
ego ya
happens what do you
está es lo que hay es lo que sucede qué
think it's not easy it's very easy but
crees que no es fácil es facilísimo pero
because of ego it doesn't end because of ego and
por ego no se hace fin por ego y por
pride just like me For example, what do I
orgullo igual que yo Por ejemplo yo que
know,
sé
eh since the last comment that
eh desde el último comentario que me
rotr made to me in the race You think
hizo rotr en la carrera Tú te crees que
I heard him talk to WhatsApp no, I haven't
yo le oído hablar al WhatsApp no no le
heard him talk to WhatsApp because I
oído hablar al WhatsApp porque todavía
'm still upset And pissed off with that race
estoy molesto Y [__] con esa carrera
when I get over the annoyance I will take him I will
cuando se me pase la molestia le cogeré
send him a WhatsApp and I will say bro what the
le mandaré un WhatsApp y le diré bro qué
[ __ ] is this right now I feel like it
[__] es esto ahora mismo tengo ganas
No, the only thing I say is what I
No yo lo único que digo es lo que digo
always say, don't go pissing off
siempre no vayáis a tocar los [__] a
other streamers no matter how much a
otros streamers por mucho que un
comment has been more or less
comentario haya estado más o menos
accurate for example Okay, well this is the
acertado por ejemplo Vale pues esto es
same but people don't have the balls to do it
lo mismo pero la gente no tiene [__]
no no no no no
hacerlo no no no no no
but it's that you can't ask
pero es que tú tampoco puedes pedirle a
people either, you can't take charge of  that
la gente tú no te puedes hacer cargo de
of what people say or don't say I
que la de lo que la gente diga o no diga
mean imagine I don't know the 3000
O sea imagínate yo no sé las 3000
people that are here right now I don't
personas que hay aquí ahora mismo yo no
know who the [ __ ] you are I don't know if you're a
sé quién [__] sois yo no sé si sois
community there will be a lot of people that aren't
comunidad habrá mucha gente que no son
from here that are just
de aquí que estén por aquí de
passing through people will have the right if they see an
paso la gente tendrá derecho de si ve un
unfortunate comment of
desafortunado
mine to comment on it no and say Hey Javi what a
mío comentarlo no y decir Oye Javi qué
disgusting comment No I don't know how you're
hasco de comentario No yo que sé tú cómo
going to ask people not to comment on
le vas a pedir a la gente no opines de
this don't comment on that I mean
esto no opines de lo otro O sea que
they make an unfortunate comment about
hacen un comentario desafortunado sobre
you and your followers are watching that
ti y tus seguidores están viendo ese
live and they say oh I don't know what you
directo y le dicen ay no sé qué tú
can't control that either One thing is
tampoco puedes controlar eso Una cosa es
that you don't order people around and another thing
que tú no mandes a la gente y otra cosa
is that you order them not to comment there's no way you
es que tú los mandes a que no opinen no
do those things it's what there is I mean
hay [__] hacer esas cosas es lo que
but because it's normal because it
hay o sea pero porque es normal porque
's a bubble that I mean the thing about
es una burbuja ese o sea lo de la
freemasonry and all that that many of you do on
masonería y demás que lo hacéis muchos
Twitter doesn't exist as such because you
Twitter no existe como tal porque os lo
're imagining it as corruption
estáis imaginando en plan corrupción
but yes everyone lives in their own
pero sí que cada uno vive en su propia
bubble you know and that is what it is  true that it
burbuja sabes y eso sí que es cierto que
's not that much of a meme and each person is very
no es tan meme y cada persona es muy
easy and it's very normal, thank God
fácil y Es muy normal yo gracias a Dios
for that I feel like every time he gets upset he stands
por eso me como que cada que se altera
up, no, he always does it standing up, it's not that I do
se pone de pie no él lo hace de pie
n't know why he does it as if he
no es que no sé por qué lo hace como si
were in the comedy club but
estuviera en el club de la comedia pero
the last few times whenever we've
las últimas veces siempre que hemos
seen Carche we see him standing up it's
visto a carche lo vemos de pie
not like that's why I'm calm,
no pasa ch Yo por eso estoy tranquilo yo
thank God I keep people in
gracias a Dios mantengo gente de mi de
my private circle, okay, if I
mi círculo privado vale que si yo la
screw something up, yeah, I don't know, Samu, for
cago en algo si yo que sé samu por
example, grabs me and says yesterday, for
ejemplo me coge y me dice ayer ayer por
example, Samu, a lifelong friend of mine, a
ejemplo samu amigo mío de toda la vida
friend of mine who has been with me since we were 11,
amigo mío que lleva conmigo desde los 11
we've been through the best and the
años hemos estado en lo mejor y en lo
worst of each other, okay, and we've been
peor de cada uno de los dos vale Y hemos
there when one of us screwed up,
estado ahí para cuando uno la cagaba
grab him and say you're [ __ ], and
[__] y decirle eres [__] y para
when the other one screwed up, you're [ __ ]
cuando el otro la cagaba eres [__]
too, okay, and he, thank God, I
también vale Y él yo gracias a Dios
have the possibility and I'm lucky
tengo la posibilidad y tengo la suerte
that in my day to day life I still have
de que en mi día a día sigo teniendo
people who tell me, hey bro, this is
personas que me dicen Oye bro esto es
a [ __ ] mess, for example, yesterday Samu
una [__] [__] por ejemplo ayer samu me
grabbed me and said, you have to be more
coge y me dice tienes que hacer más
direct, bro  you've done five live shows in
directo bro has hecho cinco directos en
the last 15 days what the [ __ ] is this
los últimos 15 días qué [__] es esto
okay And there are a lot of people who unfortunately
vale Y hay mucha gente que por desgracia
or because they have preferred to remove from their lives
o porque ha preferido apartar de su vida
Those people who tell them those things don't
A esa gente que le dice esas cosas no lo
have it and it shows on the internet and that's what it is
tiene y se nota en internet y es lo que
And it's very easy to fall into that
hay Y es que es muy fácil caer en ese
dilemma and into that problem this
dilema y en ese problema esto también
could also be a thorn in the side of
podría ser una pua para
Auron you guys think this could be
auron ustedes creéis que esto podría ser
a plla for Auron there are also people
una plla para auron también hay gente
who don't want to be told those things
que no quiere que le digan esas cosas
not to be told what's wrong or to be
no que le digan lo que está mal o que le
given advice no and they have removed from their
den consejos no y han apartado de su
lives the one who tells them things that they don't
vida al que le dicen cosas que no
want to
quieren
hear do you think this could also go that way
escuchar creéis que esto puede ir
because you have to keep in mind
ahí porque tú tienes que tener en cuenta
that if I have been able to have an
que si yo he podido llegar a tener
ego okay me who am a half dead okay
ego vale yo que soy un medio matado vale
not to be confused with pride eh with pride
no confundir con orgullo eh con orgullo
of what you have achieved and what you have
de lo que has logrado tú y de lo que has
achieved if I have achieved I
conseguido si yo he conseguido
wrote just the s what a [ __ ] timing
escito justo el s vaya [__] timing
and if I have had Pride and ego I have
e si yo he tenido Orgullo y ego yo
come to have an ego ok and there are
llegado a tener ego de acuerdo y hay
things that I can say that I have done
cosas que yo puedo decir que he hecho
well other things that I have been able to do badly
bien otras cosas que he podido hacer mal
okay and
de acuerdo
Imagine that there won't be other types of
e Imagínate que no tendrá otro tipo de
people who have had many more
gente que ha tenido muchísimos más
viewers or who have gone through stages in
viewers o que ha pasado por etapas en
which I'm not telling you that they have them
las cuales ya no te digo que los tenga
right now but that they have gone through
ahora mismo sino que ha pasado por
stages in which they have been the
etapas en las cuales han sido las
most famous people on the entire internet.
personas más famosas de todo internet
This
esto
parauro this auron This pauron is
parauro esto auron Esto pauron está
saying if I, who am nobody, have
diciendo si yo que no soy nadie he
had this ego imagine Someone who has
tenido este ego imagínate Alguien que ha
been the most no person and no longer has the
sido la persona más no y ya no tiene los
viewers that he had before, I mean he's
viewers que tenía antes o sea se está
referring to
refiriendo a
auron he's referring to auron of
auron se está refiriendo a auron
course this guy seems to me to
claro este chico a mí me parece que
have a thorn against auron save it
tiene una espinita contra auron guardar
still eh I mean he doesn't ASSUME that
todavía eh o sea él no ASUME que a lo
maybe he has done something Fe has done something
mejor él ha hecho algo Fe ha hecho algo
wrong no no no he is completely
mal no no no él está completamente
convinced that Auro has escaped
convencido de que el Auro ha escapado
well and that he has been
bien y a él le han dado
unfairly given a carche he will come back crazier than
injustamente carche volverá más loco que
ever the rats will fall No if on top of that of
nunca las ratitas caerán No si encima
course the lukewarm one has shut up and
claro encima a el tibio se ha callado y
on top of that he will come back We are all your community
encima volverá Somos todos tu comunidad
if we ever criticize you it is out of
si te criticamos alguna vez es por
affection for your work a hug churra
cariño hacia tu trabajo un abrazo churra
kiss Thank you very much both of you
beso Muchas gracias a los dos
Javi Te  I swear on my dead that until
Javi Te juro por mis muertos que hasta
the day I fall to the ground and you don't
el día que caiga al suelo y no me
pick me up I'll keep insisting on that
levantes seguiré insistiendo por ese
only with Dallas Franky delox in
only con Dallas Franky delox en
Thailand shirtless I want my album
Tailandia sin camiseta Quiero mi álbum
a kiss The other day I met delos
un beso El otro día coincidí con delos
in Madrid when I was in Madrid the
en Madrid cuando yo estaba en Madrid el
other day delos and nimu were in
otro día delos y nimu también estaban en
Madrid too but I didn't
Madrid pero yo no lo
know let's see I think I think he
sabía a ver yo creo que yo creo que él
has something saved for Auro eh I mean he
tiene guardado algo para Auro eh o sea é
has something there that until he takes it
tiene ahí algo que hasta que no se lo
away and lets it go he's not going to stop eh and he's
quite y no lo suelte no va a parar eh y
going to let it go it's just that there are already too
lo va a soltar algú es que ya ya van
many barbs eh that we see eh I mean there are
muchas puas eh que le vemos eh o sea van
many, many barbs that we see
muchas van muchas pullas que le vemos
eh there are many barbs that we see I mean
eh van muchas pullit que le vemos o sea
he is completely convinced that they have
él está completamente convencido de que
been unfair to him
con él han sido
okay
injustos vale
the last time I think we heard something
la última vez creo que escuchamos algo
that was something like the good ones are not
que era algo así como los buenos no son
that good or something like that I don't remember that you
tan buenos o algo así no me acuerdo ese
have so many secrets that in this
que tenéis tantos secretos que en esta
bubble that it's time for it to explode
burbuja que es hora de que explote
no no it's not about
no no no se trata de
that what there is is what you see the
eso lo que hay es lo que veis sea
internet is much easier than
internet es muchísimo más fácil de lo
you think
que os pensáis
some of you think maybe I'm not what do you think but what you
algunos sea yo no qué os pensáis pero lo
see is what there is and but if Auron
que veis es lo que hay y pero si auron
was lukewarm with him, yeah yeah yeah if it is
fue tibio con él ya ya ya si es que es
what I just told the superchat
lo que le acabo de decir al superchat
I say that Auron has still kept quiet
digo que todavía el auron se ha callado
and this one will come and throw something at Auron or
y llegará este y le tirará al auron o lo
take something out of him you will
sacará algo ya
see good actions like
verás acciones buenas como las acciones
bad actions obviously there are good actions that
malas obviamente hay acciones buenas que
are camouflaged behind whatever
están camufladas por detrás lo que sea
okay that I don't even know anymore I don't even know okay
vale eso yo ya ni ni me entero yo ni yo
okay look I am a
me entero vale vale fíjate que yo soy
streamer you seem to have a private guild here
streamer parces tú un gremio aquí
but what you
privado pero que no que que que que lo
see is what there is eh And whoever has
que veis es lo que hay eh Y el que tenga
two two for two in front can spin and
dos dos de dos de frente puede hilar y
can know how the [ __ ]
puede saber cómo [__] funcionan las
things work and you can know when one thing is
cosas y puedes saber cuando una cosa es
a strategy to camouflage something which is
una estrategia para camuflar algo que es
another [ __ ] etcetera is that what happens I mean is that
otra [__] etcétera es que eso pasa o
no no no think that this no that
sea es que no noos penséis que esto no
this happens today and you can
que esto sucede a día de hoy y se puede
see it and you can
ver y se puede
appreciate it is that it works like this it
apreciar es que es así funciona así
works like this in the following way if you are
funciona de la siguiente manera si tú me
going to generate something good for me  I'm going to
vas a generar algo bueno yo te voy a
bring you to my side if you're not going to generate me
traer a mi lado si no me vas a generar
well I'll take you away from my side it's a business
bueno te aparto de mi lado es un negocio
interest that I could generate in that
interés que podría generar en ese
aspect it's Ah No of course the typical eh It's that
aspecto es Ah No claro lo típico eh Es
way you clean up the image Well just like
que así se limpia la imagen Pues igual
there are people who grab me and tell me
que hay gente que me coge y me dice me
grab me and tell me no it's that of course carche
coge y me dice no es que claro carche
now you have to stop with the fans
ahora se tiene que parar con los fans
every time I go to a public event
cada vez que vaya a un evento público
because you have to clean up the
porque se tiene que limpiar la
image the first year that I was at the
imagen el primer año que estuve en la
Gamer as a recognized person which was in
Gamer como persona reconocida que fue en
2021 I stood for 4 hours 4 hours that
2021 me tiré 4 horas 4 horas de pie que
a mother with a follower had to come
tuvo que venir una madre con una
give me a sandwich and a cocoa
seguidora a darme un bocata y una cocola
my content is the same Alex El capo does not
mi contenido es el mismo Alex El capo no
approve of this comment I from Alex El
aprueba este comentario yo de Alex El
capo has content that I stick it up my
capo ha contenido que me lo meto por el
ass in fact I've said all my life
culo de hecho yo he dicho toda la vida
that Alex El capo for me is my
que Alex El capo para mí es mi creador
favorite content creator since I was little he's
de contenido favorito desde pequeñito me
going to hit me
va a pegar un petardazo
but the hit is going to hit me
pero es que el petardazo me va a dar
when I can handle it well the hit
cuando pueda llevarlo bien el petardazo
the hit is going to hit
el petardazo me va a dar a
me How
mí Cómo
How
Cómo
alis just  Look, he just put
alis la acaba de Mira le acaba de poner
a t
un t
inkosi on it. Look, the best event, without a doubt,
inkosi Mira el mejor evento sin duda
what an experience. Thanks for being our
vaya experiencia Gracias por hacernos de
guide. We had a great time. Lizy is a
guía lo pasamos genial es que es un
charmer. She's just too
Encanto lizy es que es demasiado
charming. Hey, he
encantadora
's mad that Auron left him out,
eh está ardido que auron lo dejó de lado
but I
pero
don't understand the irony of Rubius here, I
no entiendo la ironía del Rubius aquí o
mean, everyone is really screwed with the
sea están todos como muy Rayados con la
drop in viewers.
caída de de espectadores
Anyway, well, we're going to sleep.
fin Pues nos vamos í a mimir
Hey, I have to go there, well, to sleep.
eh tengo que nos vamos ahí bueno a mimir
No, I'm going there to see if I can record something. I'm
no yo voy ahí a ver si grabo algo
going to see if there's a newscast, what's on
Voy a ver si hay noticiero que lo que
regarding crime, very good. I'm going to talk about this
hay respecto a crime mu bueno Esto lo
on the news,
hablo en noticiero
guys. I'm going. I'm going. A huge hug, I
chicos me voy me voy un abrazo enorme os
love you all. Video on the
quiero mucho vídeo en el canal
main channel. Video on the main channel, it
principal vídeo en el canal principal
will open live at 7 in the morning.
abrirá directo a las 7 de la mañana
Well, let's see. A kiss.
bueno a ver ya veremos un beso
[Music]
[Música]
Family
familia